<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/" xmlns:mtree="http://www.mosets.com/tree/rss/">
<channel>
<title>Purbanchal Directory - Recently Added Listings - Television</title>
<description></description>
<link>https://pudirectory.com/</link>
<lastBuildDate>Sat, 25 Apr 2020 14:06:30 +0100</lastBuildDate>
<generator>FeedCreator 1.7.3</generator>
<item>
	<title>Makalu Television</title>
	<link>https://pudirectory.com/media/television/336-makalu-television</link>
	<description><![CDATA[
Makalu television is the first television to be broadcasted in eastern development region on 18th of Kartik 2068 .Its an initiative of renouned business personnals ,cable operaters,and people in communication and educational field.With prior permission from nepalese goverment Makalu Television is transmitted from terrestial and cable medium throughout the eastern sector of nepal.With the terrestial facility people in remote areas too can watch Makalu Television.Estimated coverage of 50 lakhs viewers it certainly reached in all the houses in eastern sector.Through our web media almost 30 lakhs views are benifitted everyday.Makalu Television is telecasted from Biratnagar an industrial capital,political and historical hub of eastern region.Focusing on the regional development Makalu Television has established its branches in cities like Dharan,Itahari,Damak,Birtamod.
Locality,Development,promotion being our slogan in a short period of time we have been able to win hearts of our viewers.
Makalu Television is an organisation dedicated on enpowering the public through deleverance of news,education,entertainment and motivation.
Makalu Television has been a symbol of pride for the people of Eastern Region.Its a duty not only to establish a common forum fro the people but also focus on its development so that it caters to all the voices from the people.
Makalu Television has played an important role in development and promotion on fields such as educational,religious,social,cultural and tourism.
In the near future Makalu Television aim to cover the whole nation.]]></description>
	<dc:creator>superadmin</dc:creator>
	<pubDate>Wed, 01 Mar 2017 08:50:23 +0100</pubDate>
	<guid>https://pudirectory.com/media/television/336-makalu-television</guid>
</item>
<item>
	<title>Himshikhar Television</title>
	<link>https://pudirectory.com/media/television/335-himshikhar-television</link>
	<description><![CDATA[
Himshikhar Television is a 24 hours complete mix channel which provides instant news, information & education. Himshikhar Television started broadcasting from 20 Kartik 2067, as private channels, We are the only channel which provides exclusive and different flavors of programs and news from outside of valley. Himshikhar Television Network is known as Nepal’s first regional television station, beaming Eastern Region. Himshikhar Television has grown significantly and has carved a niche in the broadcasting history of Nepal. It has gained equal popularity at home town and the others cities across the country. From the starting date our television is fully dedicated towards the interest of viewers so that now it is competing with national TV station through skilled manpower and output quality.

Himshikhar Television is promoted by young and energetic Himshikhar media group, it is licensed of operate as a TV broadcasting as well as terrestrially. For this purpose, it has embraced the latest technology, updated production equipment and other facilities and skilled human resources with a view to provide a multitude of entertainment programs, national and international news and talk shows. It has achieved a milestone in its stand of credible news and information and classy entertainment programs. Its objective is to provide a television service that informs, entertains and inspires viewers with a Nepalese perspective in the changing context. Himshikhar Television is now expanding its coverage area throughout the country .

Education,Information and Entertainment is our slogan.]]></description>
	<dc:creator>superadmin</dc:creator>
	<pubDate>Wed, 01 Mar 2017 08:48:30 +0100</pubDate>
	<guid>https://pudirectory.com/media/television/335-himshikhar-television</guid>
</item>
</channel>
</rss>
