<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/" xmlns:mtree="http://www.mosets.com/tree/rss/">
<channel>
<title>Purbanchal Directory - Recently Added Listings - Taxi</title>
<description></description>
<link>https://pudirectory.com/</link>
<lastBuildDate>Sat, 25 Apr 2020 13:30:08 +0100</lastBuildDate>
<generator>FeedCreator 1.7.3</generator>
<item>
	<title>New Airport Taxi Service</title>
	<link>https://pudirectory.com/taxi/2932-new-airport-taxi-service</link>
	<description><![CDATA[<img align="right" src="https://pudirectory.com/media/com_mtree/images/listings/s/698.jpg" alt="New Airport Taxi Service" />We are the best airport taxi service provider from Biratnagar and nearby areas. You can call us for booking vehicles such as scorpio, bolero, maruti etc.
 
Call us at 9843767704
Ramesh Sitaula
Itahari]]></description>
	<dc:creator>superadmin</dc:creator>
	<pubDate>Fri, 17 Jan 2020 06:55:09 +0100</pubDate>
	<guid>https://pudirectory.com/taxi/2932-new-airport-taxi-service</guid>
</item>
<item>
	<title>Hotel Pathibhara International Airport Taxi Service</title>
	<link>https://pudirectory.com/taxi/199-pathibhara-taxi-sewa</link>
	<description><![CDATA[<img align="right" src="https://pudirectory.com/media/com_mtree/images/listings/s/730.jpg" alt="Hotel Pathibhara International Airport Taxi Service" />Planning a trip to Itahari, Biratnagar, Dharan, Damak, Bhedetar, Dhankuta, Hile from airport of Biratnagar? Either alone, with the family or for business, don’t worry we’ve got you covered. We want you to enjoy what really matters and give you a stress-free travel experience wherever you are in the world, whether by taxi, train or bus. Simply search, book and Go! Just pick the date and call us and leave the rest with us. We only use the best partners in each destination to make sure you have not only the best rates but the best quality service! We have a mahindra's scorpio to pick and drop you  to promote Visit Nepal 2020.]]></description>
	<dc:creator>superadmin</dc:creator>
	<pubDate>Fri, 24 Feb 2017 12:23:47 +0100</pubDate>
	<guid>https://pudirectory.com/taxi/199-pathibhara-taxi-sewa</guid>
</item>
<item>
	<title>Nepal Auto Rental</title>
	<link>https://pudirectory.com/taxi/198-nepal-auto-rental</link>
	<description><![CDATA[
Nepal Auto Rental is a reliable 24 hour car service. We offer safe, clean and dependable car service. We're famous for fast, secure and efficient door-to-door service. We've been in business for years and pride ourselves in having courteous and friendly drivers, competitive rates, and air-conditioned vehicles for your transportation needs in Kathmandu,Nepal. We specialize in package delivery. Nepal Auto Rental, is proud to be known for the lowest rate in town. We also specialize in airport pick-ups and drop-offs.If you enjoy touring, we will be able to provide you with information on the many beautiful sights in our wonderful city.]]></description>
	<dc:creator>superadmin</dc:creator>
	<pubDate>Fri, 24 Feb 2017 12:21:56 +0100</pubDate>
	<guid>https://pudirectory.com/taxi/198-nepal-auto-rental</guid>
</item>
<item>
	<title>Airport Taxi Service</title>
	<link>https://pudirectory.com/taxi/197-airport-taxi-service</link>
	<description><![CDATA[<img align="right" src="https://pudirectory.com/media/com_mtree/images/listings/s/150.jpg" alt="Airport Taxi Service" />Airport Taxi Service for Biratnagar at special rates. Please call us @ 9842296911 or 9801110788. Place a call and book the service before your arrival at the Biratnagar Airport of vice versa.

Have a safe journey.

Ravindra Pathak
Taxi Service Biratnagar]]></description>
	<dc:creator>superadmin</dc:creator>
	<pubDate>Fri, 24 Feb 2017 12:19:23 +0100</pubDate>
	<guid>https://pudirectory.com/taxi/197-airport-taxi-service</guid>
</item>
</channel>
</rss>
