<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/" xmlns:mtree="http://www.mosets.com/tree/rss/">
<channel>
<title>Purbanchal Directory - Recently Added Listings - Real Estates</title>
<description></description>
<link>https://pudirectory.com/</link>
<lastBuildDate>Sat, 25 Apr 2020 13:29:51 +0100</lastBuildDate>
<generator>FeedCreator 1.7.3</generator>
<item>
	<title>Casa Deyra</title>
	<link>https://pudirectory.com/real-estates/903-casa-deyra</link>
	<description><![CDATA[Want to lease your Homes and Apartments on rent in Kathmandu? Casadeyra is a property management company based in Baneshwor Kathmandu, Nepal. We offer you good price of booking over your Luxury Homes and Apartments for rent. Renters don’t really care for your property but we take care of your property, Everyday.]]></description>
	<dc:creator>superadmin</dc:creator>
	<pubDate>Mon, 16 Apr 2018 07:43:34 +0100</pubDate>
	<guid>https://pudirectory.com/real-estates/903-casa-deyra</guid>
</item>
<item>
	<title>Eproperty Nepal - Buy &amp; Sale Property in Nepal</title>
	<link>https://pudirectory.com/real-estates/561-eproperty-nepal-buy-sale-property-in-nepal</link>
	<description><![CDATA[Eproperty Nepal is a real estate digital marketplace allowing simple search, study of trends, renting, marketing or Buying Properties in Nepal such that land, apartments/flats, houses, commercial buildings to potential customers all over Nepal.
We aim to make our real estate services as affordable as possible. To find and modernize thoughts for making the selling and purchasing of properties quicker, trouble-free and relaxed. So, for the leading real estate service company from Mechi to Mahakali, whereas always beyond the expectation of customer.
]]></description>
	<dc:creator>superadmin</dc:creator>
	<pubDate>Wed, 28 Jun 2017 10:07:27 +0100</pubDate>
	<guid>https://pudirectory.com/real-estates/561-eproperty-nepal-buy-sale-property-in-nepal</guid>
</item>
<item>
	<title>Birat Housing Pvt. Ltd.</title>
	<link>https://pudirectory.com/real-estates/255-birat-housing-pvt-ltd</link>
	<description><![CDATA[<img align="right" src="https://pudirectory.com/media/com_mtree/images/listings/s/181.jpg" alt="Birat Housing Pvt. Ltd." /> 
Birat Housing Company Pvt. Ltd. has been running from 10 years in Biratnagar Sub Metropolition city. It deals on properties, land and also provides the consultancy services. It was established on 2060 BS and it was started as the housing rental services and has been expanding its services to various other services where people from eastern Nepal are taking benifit from us. Birat Awas Sewa, the former company is now renamed into Birat Housing Company Pvt. Ltd., which is registered company in Company Act of Nepal and situated infront of Birendra Sabha Grihya.]]></description>
	<dc:creator>superadmin</dc:creator>
	<pubDate>Tue, 28 Feb 2017 06:05:29 +0100</pubDate>
	<guid>https://pudirectory.com/real-estates/255-birat-housing-pvt-ltd</guid>
</item>
</channel>
</rss>
