<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/" xmlns:mtree="http://www.mosets.com/tree/rss/">
<channel>
<title>Purbanchal Directory - Recently Added Listings - Fitness Center</title>
<description></description>
<link>https://pudirectory.com/</link>
<lastBuildDate>Sat, 25 Apr 2020 13:14:29 +0100</lastBuildDate>
<generator>FeedCreator 1.7.3</generator>
<item>
	<title>Nepal Yoga Institute</title>
	<link>https://pudirectory.com/fitness-center/1086-nepal-yoga-institute</link>
	<description><![CDATA[Nepal Yoga Institute, one of the most prominent place to learn Yoga in Nepal. Nepal Yoga Institute and retreat provide with the best yoga teacher training program, retreat program and stress management program.]]></description>
	<dc:creator>superadmin</dc:creator>
	<pubDate>Mon, 17 Sep 2018 08:23:55 +0100</pubDate>
	<guid>https://pudirectory.com/fitness-center/1086-nepal-yoga-institute</guid>
</item>
<item>
	<title>Nepal Yoga Home</title>
	<link>https://pudirectory.com/fitness-center/1085-nepal-yoga-home</link>
	<description><![CDATA[Yoga is an ancient form of exercise that focuses on strength, flexibility and breathing to boost physical and mental wellbeing. Nepal Yoga Home is one of the pioneer yoga school in Nepal with its outstanding performance and spiritual life-changing environment to offers all the yoga aspirants from around the world.]]></description>
	<dc:creator>superadmin</dc:creator>
	<pubDate>Mon, 17 Sep 2018 07:46:15 +0100</pubDate>
	<guid>https://pudirectory.com/fitness-center/1085-nepal-yoga-home</guid>
</item>
<item>
	<title>Boxing Incorporated East Side</title>
	<link>https://pudirectory.com/fitness-center/940-boxing-incorporated-east-side</link>
	<description><![CDATA[Get fit like a fighter and train like the best at one of our three Tucson area gyms. Our work outs burn up to 1000 calories a session. Buile lean muscle mass while burning fat and having tons of fun.
]]></description>
	<dc:creator>superadmin</dc:creator>
	<pubDate>Mon, 11 Jun 2018 13:10:07 +0100</pubDate>
	<guid>https://pudirectory.com/fitness-center/940-boxing-incorporated-east-side</guid>
</item>
<item>
	<title>Nepal Yoga Home</title>
	<link>https://pudirectory.com/fitness-center/920-nepal-yoga-home</link>
	<description><![CDATA[If you are seeking information about Yoga in Nepal then Nepal Yoga Home is the one for you. This yoga institute provides with the best Mediation Center in Nepal. It is the one of the pioneer yoga school in Nepal with its outstanding performance and spiritual life changing environment to offer all the yoga aspirants from around the world. This institute provide with the best Yoga Classes in Kathmandu with Yoga Certification in Nepal.]]></description>
	<dc:creator>superadmin</dc:creator>
	<pubDate>Mon, 07 May 2018 08:44:56 +0100</pubDate>
	<guid>https://pudirectory.com/fitness-center/920-nepal-yoga-home</guid>
</item>
<item>
	<title>Manmohan Singh</title>
	<link>https://pudirectory.com/fitness-center/900-manmohan-singh</link>
	<description><![CDATA[<img align="right" src="https://pudirectory.com/media/com_mtree/images/listings/s/438.jpg" alt="Manmohan Singh" />Rishikul Yogshala has been the leader of Yogic education since its inception in 2010. The Yoga Alliance certified Yoga school offers a vast range of programs including 200, 200, and 500 Yoga TTC along with many scholarship programs for economically unable Yoga addicts. Headquartered in the world Yoga capital, Rishikesh, the Yogshala has been spreading the sacred knowledge of Yoga in 10+ centers across five different countries- India, Nepal, Thailand, Vietnam, and Iran.

]]></description>
	<dc:creator>superadmin</dc:creator>
	<pubDate>Wed, 11 Apr 2018 11:48:28 +0100</pubDate>
	<guid>https://pudirectory.com/fitness-center/900-manmohan-singh</guid>
</item>
<item>
	<title>Yoga Teachers Training In India - Arhanta Yoga Ashram</title>
	<link>https://pudirectory.com/fitness-center/124-yoga-teachers-training-in-india-arhanta-yoga-ashram</link>
	<description><![CDATA[<img align="right" src="https://pudirectory.com/media/com_mtree/images/listings/s/80.jpg" alt="Yoga Teachers Training In India - Arhanta Yoga Ashram" />Arhanta Yoga Ashram proudly presents itself one of the leading, dedicated and famous international yoga teachers training school in india. If offers basic and advanced yoga teachers training courses in India. All courses and study materials are registered with international yoga alliance. Contact for more details : Arhanta Yoga Ashram Arhanta Yatri Niwas (Near Khajuraho), Village Bansarai, P.O. Onta Purwa (via Bamitha) District Chhatarpur Madhya Pradesh 471105, India Mr. Omkar +91 8120121002 http://www.arhantayogaindia.com]]></description>
	<dc:creator>superadmin</dc:creator>
	<pubDate>Thu, 05 Jan 2017 06:45:48 +0100</pubDate>
	<guid>https://pudirectory.com/fitness-center/124-yoga-teachers-training-in-india-arhanta-yoga-ashram</guid>
</item>
<item>
	<title>Dadhiram Recreation Complex Private Limited</title>
	<link>https://pudirectory.com/fitness-center/123-dadhiram-recreation-complex-private-limited</link>
	<description></description>
	<dc:creator>superadmin</dc:creator>
	<pubDate>Thu, 05 Jan 2017 06:42:59 +0100</pubDate>
	<guid>https://pudirectory.com/fitness-center/123-dadhiram-recreation-complex-private-limited</guid>
</item>
<item>
	<title>Sajilo Fitness and Gym</title>
	<link>https://pudirectory.com/fitness-center/122-sajilo-fitness-and-gym</link>
	<description><![CDATA[<img align="right" src="https://pudirectory.com/media/com_mtree/images/listings/s/75.jpg" alt="Sajilo Fitness and Gym" />Sajilo Fitness and Gym is located at Kanchanbari-5, Biratnagar.
 
Every person in the world would like to have a perfect body. In order to have a healthy and a strong body, people would need to consider going to a gym to work out. What do such people expect of a gym? Certainly, patrons would expect a wide selection of equipment available in a gym. Patrons would enjoy a well-educated staff who knows everything people want to know about working out. The Bally Total Fitness, located on the Boulevard, is a perfect match for that. Patrons will definitely enjoy working out at the Bally Total Fitness. What kind of environment would patrons expect? Patrons will find the Bally Total Fitness clean, well organized, and suitable for working out.
we are  world class fitness center where you can keep your body fit.
Open from 4:00AM - 10:00AM & 3:00PM - 8:00PM]]></description>
	<dc:creator>superadmin</dc:creator>
	<pubDate>Thu, 05 Jan 2017 05:27:38 +0100</pubDate>
	<guid>https://pudirectory.com/fitness-center/122-sajilo-fitness-and-gym</guid>
</item>
</channel>
</rss>
