<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/" xmlns:mtree="http://www.mosets.com/tree/rss/">
<channel>
<title>Purbanchal Directory - Recently Added Listings - Event Organizers</title>
<description></description>
<link>https://pudirectory.com/</link>
<lastBuildDate>Sat, 25 Apr 2020 13:26:19 +0100</lastBuildDate>
<generator>FeedCreator 1.7.3</generator>
<item>
	<title>The Superheroz</title>
	<link>https://pudirectory.com/event-organizers/61-the-superheroz</link>
	<description><![CDATA[THE SUPERHEROZ INCORPORATIONS, the name itself clearly signifies enthusiasm and eagerness to promote our region conglomerates a management team of young blood assembled with one theme and vision to organize events and program that can enhance the beauty and name of our city with full faith. As our city has always been like a dry zone in relation to good events or for a place to be when people want to enjoy and have fun , we the team of The SuperHeroz Inc. thought of organizing programs which in some ways entertain people, make them feel good and hopes to create a oasis of fun and enjoyment.

In the light of social responsibilities we The SuperHeroz Inc. has also thought of organizing some social welfare programs like financial support and encouraging to the needy ones like old aged homes or the orphanage homes as well as awareness programs like global warming, health awareness programs, personality development trainings and much more in the coming future not only fun and enjoyment.

Not letting people forget, we will be focusing more on cultural programs with new ideas and assuring people for no dull moments. Motivating the youths of today and believing in our nation will always be a part of our theme.]]></description>
	<dc:creator>superadmin</dc:creator>
	<pubDate>Mon, 12 Dec 2016 08:16:38 +0100</pubDate>
	<guid>https://pudirectory.com/event-organizers/61-the-superheroz</guid>
</item>
<item>
	<title>Shree Krishna Tent House</title>
	<link>https://pudirectory.com/event-organizers/60-shree-krishna-tent-house</link>
	<description></description>
	<dc:creator>superadmin</dc:creator>
	<pubDate>Mon, 12 Dec 2016 08:14:35 +0100</pubDate>
	<guid>https://pudirectory.com/event-organizers/60-shree-krishna-tent-house</guid>
</item>
<item>
	<title>Inferno event management and brand promotion</title>
	<link>https://pudirectory.com/event-organizers/59-inferno-event-management-and-brand-promotion</link>
	<description><![CDATA[<img align="right" src="https://pudirectory.com/media/com_mtree/images/listings/s/36.jpg" alt="Inferno event management and brand promotion" />We are an Event Management Company doing all Below the Line activities like mall promotions, road shows, corporate events, fashion shows, celebrity management, product launches etc

Inferno Events has the skill and expertise vital to delivering high profile event solutions and awards programs. Inferno Events has successfully managed national and localized business programs and charity related programs including the synergy of in house development in national and international levels, and production of all program elements ensures consistency and constantly delivers a superior result. Inferno Events progressive approach to new ideas and ventures means that no project is too big or small. We welcome the opportunity to discuss ways of bringing new programs or events into the public spotlight and creating greater opportunities for existing programs.

Inferno Events is a pioneer in the field of Entertainment Solution Services, Event Management Services. We always try to add a value to the projects in terms of new concepts, creativity and innovation, which sets your project apart from the rest. Efficient Project Management helps Inferno Events to remain in full control of the projects in terms of quality and timely execution. Periodic reviews throughout the design, development and execution process help us in resolving issues.

We offer a full range of services including the strategy, creative development, design, production, staging of event programs:

Corporate meetings and events , Celebrity entertainment concerts and events, Event marketing programs ,wedding planning,Product launches ,Training & Education programs,Strategic & Marketing Communications Consulting ,Related Multimedia...etc

#============================#
The Team at Inferno Events:

We the team at Inferno Events are a set of highly qualified personals working and being not only a part of Inferno Events but also working and maintaining high skilled employee status at various levels from small scale industries/business to high level corporate houses. We withstand together and feel proud to state about our status and level of prestige we maintain in terms of personality, responsibility, durability, reliability and workaholic individuals in different department.

INFERNO EVENT MANAGEMENT AND BRAND PROMOTION IS PROUD LICENSE HOLDER FOR THE FOLLOWING TITLES OF THE WORLD FOR NEPAL:-

WORLD DANCE COUNCIL - ASIAN AMATEUR LEAGUE, INDONESIA
WORLD DANCE COUNCIL - ARTISTIC DANCE DEPARTMENT, SWEDEN
MISS SUPRANATIONAL WORLD, REPUBLIC OF PANAMA
MISS CONTINENTAL ASIA-PACIFIC, FEDERAL STATE OF MICRONESIA

INFERNO EVENT MANAGEMENT AND BRAND PROMOTION UNDER THE DIRECTORSHIP OF AYUSH BARUWAL REPRESENTS AS A INTERNATIONAL DIRECTOR, CHAIRMAN, COUNTRY REPS FOR THE ABOVE TITLE AS WELL...

WORLD DANCE COUNCIL - ASIAN AMATEUR LEAGUE, INTERNATIONAL DIRECTOR - NEPAL
WORLD DANCE COUNCIL - ARTISTIC DANCE DEPARTMENT,CHAIRMAN , JOINT COMITTEE - NEPAL
MISS SUPRANATIONAL WORLD, REPUBLIC OF PAN]]></description>
	<dc:creator>superadmin</dc:creator>
	<pubDate>Mon, 12 Dec 2016 08:11:25 +0100</pubDate>
	<guid>https://pudirectory.com/event-organizers/59-inferno-event-management-and-brand-promotion</guid>
</item>
<item>
	<title>National Digital Sound</title>
	<link>https://pudirectory.com/event-organizers/58-national-digital-sound</link>
	<description><![CDATA[<img align="right" src="https://pudirectory.com/media/com_mtree/images/listings/s/32.jpg" alt="National Digital Sound" />We specialize in event management. We organize live concert, floor DJ, palki, weddings, seminars, parties.
We Provide:
- Palki- Moving chair- Flower machine- Folding stage & Generator
 
New National Brass Band
We have orchestra, sound system, digital stage lights, sangeet sandhya, mobile DJ and floor lights.]]></description>
	<dc:creator>superadmin</dc:creator>
	<pubDate>Mon, 12 Dec 2016 08:06:12 +0100</pubDate>
	<guid>https://pudirectory.com/event-organizers/58-national-digital-sound</guid>
</item>
</channel>
</rss>
