<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/" xmlns:mtree="http://www.mosets.com/tree/rss/">
<channel>
<title>Purbanchal Directory - Recently Added Listings - NGO/INGO</title>
<description></description>
<link>https://pudirectory.com/</link>
<lastBuildDate>Sat, 25 Apr 2020 13:29:28 +0100</lastBuildDate>
<generator>FeedCreator 1.7.3</generator>
<item>
	<title>The Mother Baby Center</title>
	<link>https://pudirectory.com/ngo-ingo/943-the-mother-baby-center</link>
	<description><![CDATA[We welcome you, your family, and your baby to our Coon Rapids location at Mercy Hospital with Children’s Minnesota. At The Mother Baby Center, pregnancy, childbirth and neonatal experts provide a unique, personalized experience and top-notch care throughout your childbirth journey. Our birth center is a comfortable and inviting place designed with you in mind, so you can welcome your little one into the world knowing that you and baby have the best care.
Whether you’re a first-time mom or an experienced one, The Mother Baby Center at Mercy in Coon Rapids wants to help create the birthing experience you envision. We promise to listen to your concerns and needs, and do the very best we can to exceed your expectations. We offer labor and delivery care for routine and high-risk pregnancies; home health services, integrative services, newborn care, and pain management services with non-medicinal options. For families whose babies need higher levels of care, we offer neonatal intensive care provided by pediatric experts from Children’s Minnesota.]]></description>
	<dc:creator>superadmin</dc:creator>
	<pubDate>Tue, 12 Jun 2018 17:10:41 +0100</pubDate>
	<guid>https://pudirectory.com/ngo-ingo/943-the-mother-baby-center</guid>
</item>
<item>
	<title>Hami yuwa</title>
	<link>https://pudirectory.com/ngo-ingo/438-hami-yuwa</link>
	<description><![CDATA[<img align="right" src="https://pudirectory.com/media/com_mtree/images/listings/s/254.jpg" alt="Hami yuwa" />Hami Yuwa’ is a youth led, non-governmental organization. ‘Hami Yuwa’, provide the platform for youth and help them to develop their leadership, personality, decision-making. But the main thing we do at ‘Hami Yuwa’ is we spread the positivity and moreover we believe in optimism. ‘Hami Yuwa’ actually works for youth networking. We work for youth’s skill, personality, confidence, and optimism development. We unite and motivate youth for positivity at ‘Hami Yuwa’. Youth empowerment, motivating and developing the positive vibe on youth is our mission. We believe in optimism, and potential of each youth. With our network and the main goal to make a team of altogether 660 members from 30 youths of 22 wards each of Biratnagar, regardless of their origin, ethnicity, race, and religion.]]></description>
	<dc:creator>superadmin</dc:creator>
	<pubDate>Thu, 02 Mar 2017 16:56:45 +0100</pubDate>
	<guid>https://pudirectory.com/ngo-ingo/438-hami-yuwa</guid>
</item>
<item>
	<title>Volunteer Concern</title>
	<link>https://pudirectory.com/ngo-ingo/270-volunteer-concern</link>
	<description><![CDATA[Volunteer Concern is a non-profit volunteer organization that focuses on three sides of a society: Empathy, Education and Environment. We run various community development programs within these sectors in Nepal through volunteers around the world. Volunteer Concern basically is a concern to contribute a little from your side in countries like Nepal as a volunteer. Concern here means a meaningful travel as an initiative for positive consequence. Your concern is for support, for awareness, for construction or for the compassion]]></description>
	<dc:creator>superadmin</dc:creator>
	<pubDate>Tue, 28 Feb 2017 06:30:51 +0100</pubDate>
	<guid>https://pudirectory.com/ngo-ingo/270-volunteer-concern</guid>
</item>
<item>
	<title>Youth For Blood</title>
	<link>https://pudirectory.com/ngo-ingo/269-youth-for-blood</link>
	<description><![CDATA[<img align="right" src="https://pudirectory.com/media/com_mtree/images/listings/s/184.jpg" alt="Youth For Blood" />
Youth For Blood” (YFB) is a youth-led, non-profitable, and service motivated circle of youths devoted to the welfare of blood donors and seekers in Nepal. Established in 2011 in Biratnagar, it has extended its network to 13 different cities and is still growing. One of the main objective of the organization is to manage fresh blood for people in need for free: YFB has saved over 4500 lives by managing over 6000 pints of blood and 3000 standby donors . Currently, YFB has a network of more than 50,000 blood donors throughout Nepal, 15,000 of which are registered blood donors while the remaining are people who can be reached through social networks]]></description>
	<dc:creator>superadmin</dc:creator>
	<pubDate>Tue, 28 Feb 2017 06:28:44 +0100</pubDate>
	<guid>https://pudirectory.com/ngo-ingo/269-youth-for-blood</guid>
</item>
<item>
	<title>Nepal Medical Volunteer Society Pvt Ltd.</title>
	<link>https://pudirectory.com/ngo-ingo/84-nepal-medical-volunteer-society-pvt-ltd</link>
	<description><![CDATA[<img align="right" src="https://pudirectory.com/media/com_mtree/images/listings/s/68.jpg" alt="Nepal Medical Volunteer Society Pvt Ltd." />Nepal Medical Volunteer Society in short named as NMVS was established on 1st January 2011 AD in eastern Nepal. It was formally registered on 4th September 2015 at Office of Company Registrar Kathmandu, Nepal. With the slogan of तपाई हामी सबै मिली, स्वस्थ नेपाल झिलीमिली in Nepali, we are continuously working in the field of health.]]></description>
	<dc:creator>superadmin</dc:creator>
	<pubDate>Fri, 30 Dec 2016 10:13:42 +0100</pubDate>
	<guid>https://pudirectory.com/ngo-ingo/84-nepal-medical-volunteer-society-pvt-ltd</guid>
</item>
</channel>
</rss>
