<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/" xmlns:mtree="http://www.mosets.com/tree/rss/">
<channel>
<title>Purbanchal Directory - Recently Added Listings - Drinking Water</title>
<description></description>
<link>https://pudirectory.com/</link>
<lastBuildDate>Sat, 25 Apr 2020 15:10:37 +0100</lastBuildDate>
<generator>FeedCreator 1.7.3</generator>
<item>
	<title>Ronak Traders</title>
	<link>https://pudirectory.com/drinking-water/2845-ronak-traders</link>
	<description><![CDATA[<img align="right" src="https://pudirectory.com/media/com_mtree/images/listings/s/681.jpg" alt="Ronak Traders" />We deal with Aqua sales and also provide service for water purifiers. We have all spare parts available here. Our service area ranges from school to hospital and offices to industrial area. 

Specification  - Deals in all types of RO's, Aqua Guard, and water filters with UV  and TDS controllers.. Assures  1 year guarantee with  servicing. 

Products : sediment  filters, analogue  filters, specially  deals with  blue mount  filters  and  RO's .

Mobile - 9805354592
              9804006543]]></description>
	<dc:creator>superadmin</dc:creator>
	<pubDate>Mon, 06 Jan 2020 06:33:30 +0100</pubDate>
	<guid>https://pudirectory.com/drinking-water/2845-ronak-traders</guid>
</item>
<item>
	<title>Mountain Processed Drinking Water</title>
	<link>https://pudirectory.com/drinking-water/57-mountain-processed-drinking-water</link>
	<description><![CDATA[<img align="right" src="https://pudirectory.com/media/com_mtree/images/listings/s/25.jpg" alt="Mountain Processed Drinking Water" />"Mountain" Processed Drinking Water is exceptionally well  protected by purified & protected with latest technology from USA, followed by reverse osmosis (RO), Double UV Sterilized & Ozonation.
 
We are a quality product of : Mountain Water Industries]]></description>
	<dc:creator>superadmin</dc:creator>
	<pubDate>Mon, 12 Dec 2016 07:13:36 +0100</pubDate>
	<guid>https://pudirectory.com/drinking-water/57-mountain-processed-drinking-water</guid>
</item>
<item>
	<title>Birat Nirjal Udhyog</title>
	<link>https://pudirectory.com/drinking-water/56-birat-nirjal-udhyog</link>
	<description><![CDATA[<img align="right" src="https://pudirectory.com/media/com_mtree/images/listings/s/19.jpg" alt="Birat Nirjal Udhyog" />We at Birat Nirjal Udhyog provide pure drinking water. We are situated at Kathari-5, Morang. We use UV technology as well as Reverse osmosis process for cleaning water. Drinking water, also known as potable water or improved drinking water, is water safe enough for drinking and food preparation. Globally, in 2012, 89% of the people had access to water suitable for drinking. Nearly 4 billion had access to tap water while another 2.3 billion had access to wells or public taps. 1.8 billion people still use an unsafe drinking water source which may be contaminated by feces. This can result in infectious diarrhea such as cholera and typhoid among others. Contaminated water is estimated to result in more than half a million deaths per year.]]></description>
	<dc:creator>superadmin</dc:creator>
	<pubDate>Mon, 12 Dec 2016 07:05:57 +0100</pubDate>
	<guid>https://pudirectory.com/drinking-water/56-birat-nirjal-udhyog</guid>
</item>
</channel>
</rss>
