<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/" xmlns:mtree="http://www.mosets.com/tree/rss/">
<channel>
<title>Purbanchal Directory - Recently Added Listings - Hospitals</title>
<description></description>
<link>https://pudirectory.com/</link>
<lastBuildDate>Sat, 25 Apr 2020 15:03:16 +0100</lastBuildDate>
<generator>FeedCreator 1.7.3</generator>
<item>
	<title>Sukhwinder Singh</title>
	<link>https://pudirectory.com/hospitals/general-hospital/437-sukhwinder-singh</link>
	<description><![CDATA[<img align="right" src="https://pudirectory.com/media/com_mtree/images/listings/s/253.jpg" alt="Sukhwinder Singh" />i treat sexual disorder chronic diseases piles stress with herbal medicine and shirodhara i had done certified course from national institution of medical herbalist[ENGLAND] i am member of international society of sexual medicine[holland] my website www.sanjiwanihealthcentre.com]]></description>
	<dc:creator>superadmin</dc:creator>
	<pubDate>Thu, 02 Mar 2017 09:10:32 +0100</pubDate>
	<guid>https://pudirectory.com/hospitals/general-hospital/437-sukhwinder-singh</guid>
</item>
<item>
	<title>Saptakoshi Nursing Home Pvt. Ltd.</title>
	<link>https://pudirectory.com/hospitals/general-hospital/436-saptakoshi-nursing-home-pvt-ltd</link>
	<description><![CDATA[Saptakoshi Nursing Home Pvt. Ltd.
]]></description>
	<dc:creator>superadmin</dc:creator>
	<pubDate>Thu, 02 Mar 2017 09:08:25 +0100</pubDate>
	<guid>https://pudirectory.com/hospitals/general-hospital/436-saptakoshi-nursing-home-pvt-ltd</guid>
</item>
<item>
	<title>Sagarmatha Zonal Hospital</title>
	<link>https://pudirectory.com/hospitals/general-hospital/435-sagarmatha-zonal-hospital</link>
	<description><![CDATA[Sagarmatha Zonal Hospital ]]></description>
	<dc:creator>superadmin</dc:creator>
	<pubDate>Thu, 02 Mar 2017 09:06:58 +0100</pubDate>
	<guid>https://pudirectory.com/hospitals/general-hospital/435-sagarmatha-zonal-hospital</guid>
</item>
<item>
	<title>Prasuti Sewa Kendra</title>
	<link>https://pudirectory.com/hospitals/general-hospital/434-prasuti-sewa-kendra</link>
	<description><![CDATA[Prasuti Sewa Kendra]]></description>
	<dc:creator>superadmin</dc:creator>
	<pubDate>Thu, 02 Mar 2017 09:05:41 +0100</pubDate>
	<guid>https://pudirectory.com/hospitals/general-hospital/434-prasuti-sewa-kendra</guid>
</item>
<item>
	<title>Om Sai Pathibhara Hospital &amp; Research Centre Pvt. Ltd.</title>
	<link>https://pudirectory.com/hospitals/general-hospital/433-om-sai-pathibhara-hospital-research-centre-pvt-ltd</link>
	<description><![CDATA[Om Sai Pathibhara Hospital & Research Centre Pvt. Ltd. ]]></description>
	<dc:creator>superadmin</dc:creator>
	<pubDate>Thu, 02 Mar 2017 09:04:36 +0100</pubDate>
	<guid>https://pudirectory.com/hospitals/general-hospital/433-om-sai-pathibhara-hospital-research-centre-pvt-ltd</guid>
</item>
<item>
	<title>Nobel Medical College</title>
	<link>https://pudirectory.com/hospitals/general-hospital/432-nobel-medical-college</link>
	<description><![CDATA[Nobel Medical College]]></description>
	<dc:creator>superadmin</dc:creator>
	<pubDate>Thu, 02 Mar 2017 09:03:04 +0100</pubDate>
	<guid>https://pudirectory.com/hospitals/general-hospital/432-nobel-medical-college</guid>
</item>
<item>
	<title>Neuro Hospital</title>
	<link>https://pudirectory.com/hospitals/general-hospital/431-neuro-hospital</link>
	<description><![CDATA[
About Neuro Hospital Private Hospital

NH is situated in the second largest city of Nepal, Biratnagar. This hospital is registered in Company Registration Office, Kathmandu & licensed by Ministry of Health, Government of Nepal. It is a Multidisciplinary Hundred Bedded hospital which provides services to the people not only in Eastern Region of Nepal but also in the neighborhood of North Bengal & Bihar, States of India.

The goal of Neuro Hospital is to provide curative, preventive & primitives health service with efficiency, effectiveness and assurance within the context of equality & social justice. Neuro Hospital believes that, it has all the ingredients to achieve the goal. This would help invaluable input in teaching the medical students on modern concept of hospital care besides providing good health services to the community.

Neuro Hospital is a well equipped and state-of-the-art hospital having one of the best standards and quality of care in the management of patients. It comprises of mainly neurological sciences along with other allied sciences.

The division of Neurosurgery provides 24 hours emergency, surgical and nonsurgical management of patients along with elective surgery for CNS Tumors, Pediatric Disorders and Neurovascular Surgery. Microsurgery with the use of operation microscope facilitates the preservation of vital structures and ensures satisfactory tumor removal by providing better lightning and magnification of the operative field. The operating theatre in Neuro Hospital is equipped with HR-Moller-Wedel neuro surgical microscope from Germany, the NSK Operating Drill (Japan) and other advanced instruments for patient monitoring and management. The ICU is also equipped with state of the art Intracranial pressure (ICP) Monitoring System, Blood Gas Analyzer and Advanced Vitals Monitor. We thus can manage all the neurosurgical subspecialities for the various diseases encountered in the local population.

The division of Neurology with its EEG Lab & Neuro Physiology Lab (NCV, EMG, and Evoked Potential) provides neuromedical treatment of Seizure & Movement Disorders along with management of stroke and peripheral neuropathy. Sleep disorder management with use of sleep laboratory is in the planning. The department of radiology provides 24 hours computed imaging of brain and spinal cord which gives better knowledge about normal and diseased central nervous system. It is supported with use of Pathology, USG and intraop radiology. Allied specialties like General Surgery, Internal Medicine, Orthopedics, Physiotherapy and ENT provide support in the management of both traumatic and non-traumatic cases. Division of Obstetrics & Gynecology and Pediatrics provides services to the people along with Ophthalmology, Dermatology & Dental Services.]]></description>
	<dc:creator>superadmin</dc:creator>
	<pubDate>Thu, 02 Mar 2017 08:57:36 +0100</pubDate>
	<guid>https://pudirectory.com/hospitals/general-hospital/431-neuro-hospital</guid>
</item>
<item>
	<title>National Medical &amp; Research Centre (P) Ltd.</title>
	<link>https://pudirectory.com/hospitals/general-hospital/430-national-medical-research-centre-p-ltd</link>
	<description><![CDATA[National Medical & Research Centre (P) Ltd.]]></description>
	<dc:creator>superadmin</dc:creator>
	<pubDate>Thu, 02 Mar 2017 08:55:06 +0100</pubDate>
	<guid>https://pudirectory.com/hospitals/general-hospital/430-national-medical-research-centre-p-ltd</guid>
</item>
<item>
	<title>Mission Hospital</title>
	<link>https://pudirectory.com/hospitals/general-hospital/429-mission-hospital</link>
	<description><![CDATA[Mission Hospital ]]></description>
	<dc:creator>superadmin</dc:creator>
	<pubDate>Thu, 02 Mar 2017 08:53:33 +0100</pubDate>
	<guid>https://pudirectory.com/hospitals/general-hospital/429-mission-hospital</guid>
</item>
<item>
	<title>Mechi Zonal Hospital</title>
	<link>https://pudirectory.com/hospitals/general-hospital/428-mechi-zonal-hospital</link>
	<description><![CDATA[Mechi Zonal Hospital ]]></description>
	<dc:creator>superadmin</dc:creator>
	<pubDate>Thu, 02 Mar 2017 08:51:23 +0100</pubDate>
	<guid>https://pudirectory.com/hospitals/general-hospital/428-mechi-zonal-hospital</guid>
</item>
<item>
	<title>Koshi Nursing Home</title>
	<link>https://pudirectory.com/hospitals/general-hospital/427-koshi-nursing-home</link>
	<description><![CDATA[Koshi Nursing Home ]]></description>
	<dc:creator>superadmin</dc:creator>
	<pubDate>Thu, 02 Mar 2017 08:49:29 +0100</pubDate>
	<guid>https://pudirectory.com/hospitals/general-hospital/427-koshi-nursing-home</guid>
</item>
<item>
	<title>Jyoti Homeo Clinic</title>
	<link>https://pudirectory.com/hospitals/general-hospital/426-jyoti-homeo-clinic</link>
	<description><![CDATA[Jyoti Homeo Clinic]]></description>
	<dc:creator>superadmin</dc:creator>
	<pubDate>Thu, 02 Mar 2017 08:48:16 +0100</pubDate>
	<guid>https://pudirectory.com/hospitals/general-hospital/426-jyoti-homeo-clinic</guid>
</item>
<item>
	<title>Dharan Hospital</title>
	<link>https://pudirectory.com/hospitals/general-hospital/425-dharan-hospital</link>
	<description><![CDATA[Dharan Hospital ]]></description>
	<dc:creator>superadmin</dc:creator>
	<pubDate>Thu, 02 Mar 2017 08:47:07 +0100</pubDate>
	<guid>https://pudirectory.com/hospitals/general-hospital/425-dharan-hospital</guid>
</item>
<item>
	<title>Care Medical Centre (P) Ltd.</title>
	<link>https://pudirectory.com/hospitals/general-hospital/424-care-medical-centre-p-ltd</link>
	<description><![CDATA[Care Medical Centre (P) Ltd. ]]></description>
	<dc:creator>superadmin</dc:creator>
	<pubDate>Thu, 02 Mar 2017 08:45:24 +0100</pubDate>
	<guid>https://pudirectory.com/hospitals/general-hospital/424-care-medical-centre-p-ltd</guid>
</item>
<item>
	<title>AMDA-Hospital</title>
	<link>https://pudirectory.com/hospitals/general-hospital/423-amda-hospital</link>
	<description><![CDATA[AMDA-Hospital ]]></description>
	<dc:creator>superadmin</dc:creator>
	<pubDate>Thu, 02 Mar 2017 08:43:36 +0100</pubDate>
	<guid>https://pudirectory.com/hospitals/general-hospital/423-amda-hospital</guid>
</item>
<item>
	<title>Abadha Narayan Nursing Home</title>
	<link>https://pudirectory.com/hospitals/general-hospital/422-abadha-narayan-nursing-home</link>
	<description><![CDATA[
Abadha Narayan Nursing Home]]></description>
	<dc:creator>superadmin</dc:creator>
	<pubDate>Thu, 02 Mar 2017 08:41:53 +0100</pubDate>
	<guid>https://pudirectory.com/hospitals/general-hospital/422-abadha-narayan-nursing-home</guid>
</item>
<item>
	<title>Morang Sahakari Hospital</title>
	<link>https://pudirectory.com/hospitals/general-hospital/421-morang-sahakari-hospital</link>
	<description><![CDATA[
Morang Sahakari Hospital is situated at the heart of Biratnagar at Sansari Maisthan.
 ]]></description>
	<dc:creator>superadmin</dc:creator>
	<pubDate>Thu, 02 Mar 2017 08:40:47 +0100</pubDate>
	<guid>https://pudirectory.com/hospitals/general-hospital/421-morang-sahakari-hospital</guid>
</item>
<item>
	<title>Lifeguard Hospital Pvt. Ltd.</title>
	<link>https://pudirectory.com/hospitals/general-hospital/420-lifeguard-hospital-pvt-ltd</link>
	<description><![CDATA[<img align="right" src="https://pudirectory.com/media/com_mtree/images/listings/s/248.png" alt="Lifeguard Hospital Pvt. Ltd." />Lifeguard Hospital Pvt. Ltd.
Life Guard Hospital Pvt. Ltd. referred to as LG started as a Life Guard Diagnosis & Pathology Center in 6 October 2004 (20 Ashoj 2061) with a philanthropic vision of serving the mankind and contributing to the health sector of Nepal. The name itself describe that it has started its operation as a diagnostic center. Life guard hospital is dedicated to the “Patient first” with a team of specialists working together, along with the best technology available today to optimize patient outcome.
 
The hospital has constructed its own building in the Bargachhi area of Biratnagar and started its operation with Siemens make Double Slice CT Scanner System- SOMATOM Emotion Duo services to the patients in the new premises. We have 6 kattha lands and constructed our state-of-the-art technology building covering more than 30,000 sq. ft.]]></description>
	<dc:creator>superadmin</dc:creator>
	<pubDate>Thu, 02 Mar 2017 08:38:24 +0100</pubDate>
	<guid>https://pudirectory.com/hospitals/general-hospital/420-lifeguard-hospital-pvt-ltd</guid>
</item>
<item>
	<title>Biratnagar Aspatal Pvt Ltd</title>
	<link>https://pudirectory.com/hospitals/general-hospital/419-biratnagar-aspatal-pvt-ltd</link>
	<description><![CDATA[<img align="right" src="https://pudirectory.com/media/com_mtree/images/listings/s/245.jpg" alt="Biratnagar Aspatal Pvt Ltd" />We believe that everyone in our community deserves the finest healthcare. And in order to make true on this belief, we're committed to being the best at everything we do. Since being established, more than 19 years ago, Biratnagar Aspatal, has worked towards achieving its principle.  Our team of doctors, nurses, volunteers, pharmacists, managers, administrators, and support staff work as a team to help us uphold the culture of excellence we strive. We're inspired to stay abreast of the newest medical technologies and procedures, and to make every effort for constant improvements. This pursuit of excellence, along with the competence of our Doctor's, has led us to national recognition and benchmark performance in many areas. With the help of state-of-the-art technological developments, and constant reinvestments into newest technologies, Biratnagar Aspatal has managed to provide advanced patient care that were inaccessible through previous traditional procedures; thus ensuring maximum recovery. So, why Biratnagar Aspatal Pvt. Ltd?  Because better healthcare for you begins here with us. Our team assumes great responsibility for each and every patient admitted. Our model of care and treatment provides individualized treatment, consultation and services to meet your unique needs - because no two patients are ever alike.]]></description>
	<dc:creator>superadmin</dc:creator>
	<pubDate>Thu, 02 Mar 2017 08:34:31 +0100</pubDate>
	<guid>https://pudirectory.com/hospitals/general-hospital/419-biratnagar-aspatal-pvt-ltd</guid>
</item>
<item>
	<title>Birat Nursing &amp; Maternity Home</title>
	<link>https://pudirectory.com/hospitals/nursing-home/418-birat-nursing-maternity-home</link>
	<description><![CDATA[Birat Nursing & Maternity Home ]]></description>
	<dc:creator>superadmin</dc:creator>
	<pubDate>Thu, 02 Mar 2017 07:10:42 +0100</pubDate>
	<guid>https://pudirectory.com/hospitals/nursing-home/418-birat-nursing-maternity-home</guid>
</item>
<item>
	<title>Abadha Narayan Nursing Home</title>
	<link>https://pudirectory.com/hospitals/nursing-home/417-abadha-narayan-nursing-home</link>
	<description><![CDATA[Abadha Narayan Nursing Home ]]></description>
	<dc:creator>superadmin</dc:creator>
	<pubDate>Thu, 02 Mar 2017 07:08:42 +0100</pubDate>
	<guid>https://pudirectory.com/hospitals/nursing-home/417-abadha-narayan-nursing-home</guid>
</item>
<item>
	<title>Mount Everest Homoeo Medico</title>
	<link>https://pudirectory.com/hospitals/homeopathic/416-mount-everest-homoeo-medico</link>
	<description><![CDATA[<img align="right" src="https://pudirectory.com/media/com_mtree/images/listings/s/244.jpg" alt="Mount Everest Homoeo Medico" />Mount Everest Homoeo Medico
Homoeopathic treatment Center]]></description>
	<dc:creator>superadmin</dc:creator>
	<pubDate>Thu, 02 Mar 2017 07:07:10 +0100</pubDate>
	<guid>https://pudirectory.com/hospitals/homeopathic/416-mount-everest-homoeo-medico</guid>
</item>
<item>
	<title>Taparia Eye Care Pvt.Ltd.</title>
	<link>https://pudirectory.com/hospitals/eye-hospital/415-taparia-eye-care-pvt-ltd</link>
	<description><![CDATA[<img align="right" src="https://pudirectory.com/media/com_mtree/images/listings/s/243.jpg" alt="Taparia Eye Care Pvt.Ltd." />Taparia Eye Care Pvt.Ltd. ]]></description>
	<dc:creator>superadmin</dc:creator>
	<pubDate>Thu, 02 Mar 2017 07:04:15 +0100</pubDate>
	<guid>https://pudirectory.com/hospitals/eye-hospital/415-taparia-eye-care-pvt-ltd</guid>
</item>
<item>
	<title>Biratnagar Eye Hospital</title>
	<link>https://pudirectory.com/hospitals/eye-hospital/414-biratnagar-eye-hospital</link>
	<description><![CDATA[<img align="right" src="https://pudirectory.com/media/com_mtree/images/listings/s/242.jpg" alt="Biratnagar Eye Hospital" /> (www.erec-p.org)
Biratnagar Eye Hospital is a non-profitable, charitable eye hospital. It delivers affordable high quality eye care services to the economically poor and under-privileged people of the community. This hospital is an extension of Sagarmatha Choudhary Eye Hospital in Lahan started in September 2006.]]></description>
	<dc:creator>superadmin</dc:creator>
	<pubDate>Thu, 02 Mar 2017 07:02:27 +0100</pubDate>
	<guid>https://pudirectory.com/hospitals/eye-hospital/414-biratnagar-eye-hospital</guid>
</item>
<item>
	<title>Rugveda Fracture and Orthopedic Hospital</title>
	<link>https://pudirectory.com/hospitals/413-rugveda-fracture-and-orthopedic-hospital</link>
	<description><![CDATA[<img align="right" src="https://pudirectory.com/media/com_mtree/images/listings/s/241.jpg" alt="Rugveda Fracture and Orthopedic Hospital" />
Rugveda Orthopaedic Hospital - The Best Joint Replacement, Fracture Care and Orthopaedic Centre! They provide the most accurate and reasonable medical services at an excellent quality. Rugveda Hospital specializes in Orthopaedic Treatments including total knee replacement, total hip replacement, spinal care, broken/injured bone treatments. Dr. Mihir Mehta is a highly regarded Orthopaedic Consultant and Joint Replacement Surgeon in India. Since 2006, Dr. Mihir has been successfully running Rugveda Hospital in Vasna, Ahmedabad (Gujarat). His clinical profile includes a state-of-the-art technical setup and caring patient care. His orthopaedic services are performed along with high-tech instruments and methods. He has a highly qualified medical team. Orthopaedic services provided herein are truly accurate and greatly successful. His Medical Expertise Dr. Mihir has come across a long medical travel. His presence, academic gains and practical exposure in orthopaedic are largely appreciable. He has a vast field experience of as many as 5000 orthopaedic surgeries operated across many leading hospitals. He has successfully done around 2000 joint replacement surgeries too. He is always keen to get updated in his surgical skills and field knowledge. He frequently travels nationally and internationally to know much about his medical skills and give appropriate orthopaedic solutions to all. Dr. Mihir Mehta has effectively advanced the most unique “Fast Track Joint Replacement Surgery. Through this, he offers his patients the most precise, safest, least painful, quickest surgery and post-surgical recovery. The procedure does not require more physiotherapy sessions as well. The patients get high-level of knee mobility sooner after the surgery. The total hip replacement procedure together with other orthopaedic care is just similar in functions and results. He and his medical staff are purely excellent in performing the computer-navigated joint replacement surgeries. The Rugveda Hospital works on the belief of “Application of Knowledge for Service of Mankind” in order to achieve the greatest patient care and highest quality life!!!!]]></description>
	<dc:creator>superadmin</dc:creator>
	<pubDate>Thu, 02 Mar 2017 06:59:26 +0100</pubDate>
	<guid>https://pudirectory.com/hospitals/413-rugveda-fracture-and-orthopedic-hospital</guid>
</item>
</channel>
</rss>
