<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/" xmlns:mtree="http://www.mosets.com/tree/rss/">
<channel>
<title>Purbanchal Directory - Recently Added Listings - Travel Agencies</title>
<description></description>
<link>https://pudirectory.com/</link>
<lastBuildDate>Sat, 25 Apr 2020 13:30:48 +0100</lastBuildDate>
<generator>FeedCreator 1.7.3</generator>
<item>
	<title>JAYA GANGA TOURS &amp; TRAVEL(PVT.LTD)</title>
	<link>https://pudirectory.com/travel-agencies/2568-jaya-ganga-tours-travel-pvt-ltd</link>
	<description><![CDATA[<img align="right" src="https://pudirectory.com/media/com_mtree/images/listings/s/641.jpeg" alt="JAYA GANGA TOURS & TRAVEL(PVT.LTD)" />Jaya Ganga tours & travels: - looking for business travels packages. Let us help you find great results! Your travels experience is our priority.
We are here for:
 Train tickets, Domestic & International Flights, Visa process and Tour packages. 
]]></description>
	<dc:creator>prakash</dc:creator>
	<pubDate>Tue, 26 Nov 2019 14:29:18 +0100</pubDate>
	<guid>https://pudirectory.com/travel-agencies/2568-jaya-ganga-tours-travel-pvt-ltd</guid>
</item>
<item>
	<title>Jag Bahadur Budha</title>
	<link>https://pudirectory.com/travel-agencies/1244-jag-bahadur-budha</link>
	<description><![CDATA[Himalayan Companion Treks and Expedition Pvt.Ltd. is a truly your holiday Companion in Nepal’

To provide Excellency adventure service in Himalaya, by keeping the center in our valued client, personnel, and local people, and nature. To explore the hidden valleys with cooperation and coordination with local people, development agencies, government agencies, and bring them into the mainstream of tourism. To promote the local heritages, culture and traditions, nature and ecology through the quest of new hidden trails. Himalayan Companion is envisioned for a sustainable development of Himalayan life through sustainable tourism.]]></description>
	<dc:creator>superadmin</dc:creator>
	<pubDate>Tue, 22 Jan 2019 09:25:06 +0100</pubDate>
	<guid>https://pudirectory.com/travel-agencies/1244-jag-bahadur-budha</guid>
</item>
<item>
	<title>Exciting Nepal Treks and Expedition P.Ltd.</title>
	<link>https://pudirectory.com/travel-agencies/968-exciting-nepal-treks-and-expedition-p-ltd</link>
	<description><![CDATA[Exciting Nepal Treks & Expedition Pvt. Ltd. is located in Kathmandu. Exciting Nepal Treks & Expedition Pvt. Ltd. is working in Travel agencies activities. You can contact the company at 01-4701298. You can find more information about Exciting Nepal Treks & Expedition Pvt. Ltd. at www.excitingnepal.com. You can contact the company by email at info@excitingnepal.com.]]></description>
	<dc:creator>superadmin</dc:creator>
	<pubDate>Sat, 23 Jun 2018 01:35:21 +0100</pubDate>
	<guid>https://pudirectory.com/travel-agencies/968-exciting-nepal-treks-and-expedition-p-ltd</guid>
</item>
<item>
	<title>Global Holidays Adventure</title>
	<link>https://pudirectory.com/travel-agencies/948-global-holidays-adventure</link>
	<description><![CDATA[<img align="right" src="https://pudirectory.com/media/com_mtree/images/listings/s/457.jpg" alt="Global Holidays Adventure" />Global Holidays Adventure Pvt. Ltd is a government registered trekking company adminstered by the highly qualified, motivated and result-oriented professional trekking and tour leaders of Nepal to promote adventure tourism within Nepal, Tibet and Bhutan.]]></description>
	<dc:creator>superadmin</dc:creator>
	<pubDate>Thu, 14 Jun 2018 06:57:35 +0100</pubDate>
	<guid>https://pudirectory.com/travel-agencies/948-global-holidays-adventure</guid>
</item>
<item>
	<title>Global Holidays Adventure</title>
	<link>https://pudirectory.com/travel-agencies/947-global-holidays-adventure</link>
	<description><![CDATA[<img align="right" src="https://pudirectory.com/media/com_mtree/images/listings/s/456.jpg" alt="Global Holidays Adventure" />Global Holidays Adventure Pvt. Ltd is a government registered trekking company adminstered by the highly qualified, motivated and result-oriented professional trekking and tour leaders of Nepal to promote adventure tourism within Nepal, Tibet and Bhutan.]]></description>
	<dc:creator>superadmin</dc:creator>
	<pubDate>Thu, 14 Jun 2018 06:57:32 +0100</pubDate>
	<guid>https://pudirectory.com/travel-agencies/947-global-holidays-adventure</guid>
</item>
<item>
	<title>Reasonable Treks And Tour</title>
	<link>https://pudirectory.com/travel-agencies/931-reasonable-treks-and-tour</link>
	<description><![CDATA[Reasonable Treks and Tour is local base holiday operator
Reasonable Treks and Tour team ensures a complete holiday experience to suit requirements of an individual or a group and fulfills yours dream of climbing, walking, hiking,trekking in the great Himalayas of Nepal & Tibet. We are a pioneer Nepal’s government registered trekking agency based in Kathmandu. The only paradise lies in the world is Nepal. To the adventures lovers, Trekking in Nepal is an experience of many proportion.

We offer the best and most personalized travel services. When you come with us, all services are included, leaving you free to enjoy the beauty around you and respond to the warmth of people who have not forgotten to maintain the integrity of our natural environment. Relax and give yourself time to enjoy a unique holiday with us. We do not force you follow our day to day pre-planned itinerary; it can be minimized as well as prolong on your requirements. This trekking agency in Nepalcan arrange the trip in any period of time. The only thing you need to do is choose a plan we will do the work of organizing that perfectly matches with your holiday plan.]]></description>
	<dc:creator>superadmin</dc:creator>
	<pubDate>Sun, 20 May 2018 14:20:07 +0100</pubDate>
	<guid>https://pudirectory.com/travel-agencies/931-reasonable-treks-and-tour</guid>
</item>
<item>
	<title>Exciting Nepal Treks and Expedition P.Ltd.</title>
	<link>https://pudirectory.com/travel-agencies/928-exciting-nepal-treks-and-expedition-p-ltd</link>
	<description><![CDATA[Exciting Nepal Treks and Expedition Pvt. Ltd. is a registered with the department of Tourism, Government of Nepal since 2006 as a 
travel company based in Kathmandu that offers the widest range 
of adventurous outdoor activities especially in Nepal, Tibet, as 
well as Bhutan.]]></description>
	<dc:creator>superadmin</dc:creator>
	<pubDate>Thu, 17 May 2018 03:18:09 +0100</pubDate>
	<guid>https://pudirectory.com/travel-agencies/928-exciting-nepal-treks-and-expedition-p-ltd</guid>
</item>
<item>
	<title>Shera sherpa adventures</title>
	<link>https://pudirectory.com/travel-agencies/921-shera-sherpa-adventures</link>
	<description><![CDATA[Shera sherpa adventutres is best trekking agency in nepal. We are the most experienced trekking agency in nepal from the years . If you are looking for extreme adventure and superb experience through your journey than book us and enjoy the thrills of  trekking with us.]]></description>
	<dc:creator>superadmin</dc:creator>
	<pubDate>Thu, 10 May 2018 17:01:54 +0100</pubDate>
	<guid>https://pudirectory.com/travel-agencies/921-shera-sherpa-adventures</guid>
</item>
<item>
	<title>Nepal Planet Treks expedition</title>
	<link>https://pudirectory.com/travel-agencies/904-nepal-planet-treks-expedition</link>
	<description><![CDATA[Nepal Planet Treks & Expeditions welcomes you to Nepal the country of the Himalayas, started in 2014 Nepal Planet Treks & Expeditions is one the new and innovated agencies in Nepal. Our Managing Director/Trekking Guide Mr. Sanjib Adhikari has over 18 years of trekking experience and always looks for the newest and unexplored routes to increase your trekking experience. Offering all activities such as; trekking, touring, mountaineering, adventure sports, volunteering, paragliding, jungle safaris, mountain flights and many more Nepal Planet Treks & Expeditions promises you a lifetime of memories on a single trip! Nepal Planet Treks & Expeditions offers the newest way of trekking by letting our guests modify the routes to just explore a bit further in to the beautiful landscape of Nepal. Dealing in sustainable tourism we provide jobs for the local communities by hiring porters directly from the local villages, booking at the local teahouses provides a sustainable income for the rural areas in Nepal. Our Nepal Mountain Guide Team provides you with the best service so that you as our valued guest can enjoy the utmost of your well-deserved holiday/trek. In our team]]></description>
	<dc:creator>superadmin</dc:creator>
	<pubDate>Wed, 18 Apr 2018 02:38:40 +0100</pubDate>
	<guid>https://pudirectory.com/travel-agencies/904-nepal-planet-treks-expedition</guid>
</item>
<item>
	<title>Royal Mountain Trekking Pvt. Ltd.</title>
	<link>https://pudirectory.com/travel-agencies/902-royal-mountain-trekking-pvt-ltd</link>
	<description><![CDATA[<img align="right" src="https://pudirectory.com/media/com_mtree/images/listings/s/439.jpg" alt="Royal Mountain Trekking Pvt. Ltd." />Royal Mountain Trekking (RMT) is Nepal Based company focused on local travel, trekking and peak climbing adventure operated by team of experienced, dedicated Sherpa guide. stablished in 1992, having more than 2 decades of experience operating  A team of experienced 
guides, cooks and Sherpa supports bringing a wealth of trekking experience in the Himalayas.]]></description>
	<dc:creator>superadmin</dc:creator>
	<pubDate>Sun, 15 Apr 2018 05:51:02 +0100</pubDate>
	<guid>https://pudirectory.com/travel-agencies/902-royal-mountain-trekking-pvt-ltd</guid>
</item>
<item>
	<title>Everest base camp trekking</title>
	<link>https://pudirectory.com/travel-agencies/892-everest-base-camp-trekking</link>
	<description><![CDATA[Everest Base Camp trekking is one of the classical and popular trekking trail that started in 1953 from Nepal side. Generally, trekkers love two weeks trek starting and concluding at Lukla, the airport at the south of Sagarmatha National Park. However, alternativey you may start from Jiri spending extra ten days before Phakding. The trail continues via upper Phakding and it follows the Dudh Kosi valley that climbs up to the Sherpa capital of Namche Bazzar which is the junction for every trekker to the Everest region. Villages and magnificent rhododendron, magnolia and giant fire forests are intermingled in the region. Enroute, you will pass through Thyangboche monastery, Pangboche and Pheriche villages, rich in Sherpa culture and traditions. The trail follows Khumbu Glacier upto Lobuche, a best point to view the scene of Ama Dablam, Tawache and other peaks then trail leads Gorak Shep. Mount Kala pattar(5554m) is the final destination of this trek which offers the breathtaking views of Himalayan giant, literally, freezing your senses with breathless admiration that beholds the eye; and makes up for the lung stuffed climb that took you up to there.]]></description>
	<dc:creator>superadmin</dc:creator>
	<pubDate>Fri, 30 Mar 2018 09:09:41 +0100</pubDate>
	<guid>https://pudirectory.com/travel-agencies/892-everest-base-camp-trekking</guid>
</item>
<item>
	<title>Enjoy Nepal Treks Expedition &amp; Tours P.Ltd.</title>
	<link>https://pudirectory.com/travel-agencies/888-enjoy-nepal-treks-expedition-tours-p-ltd</link>
	<description><![CDATA[<img align="right" src="https://pudirectory.com/media/com_mtree/images/listings/s/428.jpg" alt="Enjoy Nepal Treks Expedition & Tours P.Ltd." />Dear Nepal Travelers Namaste!
My name is Ras Bahadur rai from the east part of Nepal Everest Region(Solukhumbu).I have an experience in tourism since 2008.I am a Government licensed Trekking Guide in Nepal.
As well owner at  Enjoy Nepal Treks Expedition & Tours Pvt.Ltd.  www.enjoynepaltreks.com 
I have been all part of Nepal  in Nepal Trekking Himalayas  Regions and Routes  as porter ,Cook and Guide.(Everest Region,Annapurna Region,Mustang Region,Manaslu Region,Dolpo Region,Kanchenjunga ,Langtang Region,Arun Valley, all most all trekking region in Nepal.

If you like to ask about the Nepal,Nepal Trekking,Peak Climbing ,Guide, Porter if you like to Nepal Trek with me, write me E-mail at any time.It's me available for all Nepal Trekking Regions and Trekking season.Thanks!

Guide license: 6204
Guide Experience: 8 Years (agency employed)
Nationality: Nepali
Language speak: English & Germany
 




]]></description>
	<dc:creator>superadmin</dc:creator>
	<pubDate>Thu, 22 Mar 2018 12:56:54 +0100</pubDate>
	<guid>https://pudirectory.com/travel-agencies/888-enjoy-nepal-treks-expedition-tours-p-ltd</guid>
</item>
<item>
	<title>Mountain mart Treks and expeditions</title>
	<link>https://pudirectory.com/travel-agencies/885-mountain-mart-treks-and-expeditions</link>
	<description><![CDATA[A leading Travel and Tour Agency for Mountaineering and peak climbing in the trek routes and climbing peaks like Mera peak.]]></description>
	<dc:creator>superadmin</dc:creator>
	<pubDate>Sun, 18 Mar 2018 08:13:14 +0100</pubDate>
	<guid>https://pudirectory.com/travel-agencies/885-mountain-mart-treks-and-expeditions</guid>
</item>
<item>
	<title>Mardi Himal Trek</title>
	<link>https://pudirectory.com/travel-agencies/868-mardi-himal-trek</link>
	<description><![CDATA[Mardi Himal Trek is the shortest and the best scenic trail to reach at the base of the Mountain. During  the trek, here is no time to blink your eyes. While trekking the views of  Annapurna, Dhaulagiri, Machhapuchhre & Manaslu Himalaya come’s in front of you. The Mardi Himal Trek was opened to tourist in 2012. This trial contains beautiful rotendent forests to snowy, rocky hills.
http://www.himalayanmonk.com/packages/mardi-himal-trek-short-trek-in-nepal/:]]></description>
	<dc:creator>superadmin</dc:creator>
	<pubDate>Tue, 27 Feb 2018 05:45:23 +0100</pubDate>
	<guid>https://pudirectory.com/travel-agencies/868-mardi-himal-trek</guid>
</item>
<item>
	<title>Quick Trip Removals Ltd</title>
	<link>https://pudirectory.com/travel-agencies/859-quick-trip-removals-ltd</link>
	<description><![CDATA[Quick trip Removals are a Greater London based Removals Company with May years’ experience. They offer removal services in London including packing and delivery. We can offer a full removals service including packing & delivery. For booking quick trip Removals, call now 02031989198]]></description>
	<dc:creator>superadmin</dc:creator>
	<pubDate>Fri, 16 Feb 2018 10:07:14 +0100</pubDate>
	<guid>https://pudirectory.com/travel-agencies/859-quick-trip-removals-ltd</guid>
</item>
<item>
	<title>Wave Travels And Tours Pvt. Ltd.</title>
	<link>https://pudirectory.com/travel-agencies/718-wave-travels-and-tours-pvt-ltd</link>
	<description><![CDATA[Wave Travels And Tours Pvt. Ltd. is located in Biratnagar, Nepal. Company is working in Travel agents business activities.]]></description>
	<dc:creator>pdmt</dc:creator>
	<pubDate>Thu, 11 Jan 2018 10:50:24 +0100</pubDate>
	<guid>https://pudirectory.com/travel-agencies/718-wave-travels-and-tours-pvt-ltd</guid>
</item>
<item>
	<title>Pro Nepaltour</title>
	<link>https://pudirectory.com/travel-agencies/710-pro-nepaltour</link>
	<description><![CDATA[<img align="right" src="https://pudirectory.com/media/com_mtree/images/listings/s/408.jpg" alt="Pro Nepaltour" />At Pro Nepal Tours, we provide you with the best all-inclusive travel packages to Nepal. Our professional guides have more than 10 years experience and speak multiple languages so you will be able to experience Nepal as a local.]]></description>
	<dc:creator>superadmin</dc:creator>
	<pubDate>Tue, 09 Jan 2018 09:22:20 +0100</pubDate>
	<guid>https://pudirectory.com/travel-agencies/710-pro-nepaltour</guid>
</item>
<item>
	<title>Ram Chandra Adhikari</title>
	<link>https://pudirectory.com/travel-agencies/706-ram-chandra-adhikari</link>
	<description><![CDATA[It is my great pleasure to introduce our self as a tour, trekking & expedition operator in Nepal, Tibet, Bhutan, & India. We are eagerly welcome you at our great country of Himalayan Ranges of Nepal. The company has dedicated, dynamic travel expert since its establishment. We are proud to be express our aim is to be full fill our customer satisfaction during the travel vacation in Nepal/Tibet/Bhutan as well as other destination. Our team will be right hand in your tour & trekking packages as well as other services.
Limitless Vacation Pvt. Ltd.  Operates Muktinath yatra, Kailash yatra, Pashupatianth Yatra, cultural tours, special interest tours, adventure tours and trekking along with meetings, incentives, conferences, hotel bookings, domestic and international ticketing. All tours can be tailor made to meet our client's specific requirements. The company in essence provides complete destination management for our varied clientele.
The office of Limitless Vacation Pvt. Ltd is very centrally located in the business and tourist hub of the city at Soalteemod. We assure our clients the best possible services that can be provided in Nepal due to our experience, expertise and infrastructure.
Looking forward to welcome you in the land of the Himalayan kingdom of Nepal.
]]></description>
	<dc:creator>superadmin</dc:creator>
	<pubDate>Thu, 28 Dec 2017 06:54:10 +0100</pubDate>
	<guid>https://pudirectory.com/travel-agencies/706-ram-chandra-adhikari</guid>
</item>
<item>
	<title>The Everest Holiday</title>
	<link>https://pudirectory.com/travel-agencies/696-the-everest-holiday</link>
	<description><![CDATA[<img align="right" src="https://pudirectory.com/media/com_mtree/images/listings/s/401.jpg" alt="The Everest Holiday" />The organization has provided excellent service to hundreds of visitors giving extreme value on clients and guests requirements.

]]></description>
	<dc:creator>superadmin</dc:creator>
	<pubDate>Fri, 08 Dec 2017 08:32:20 +0100</pubDate>
	<guid>https://pudirectory.com/travel-agencies/696-the-everest-holiday</guid>
</item>
<item>
	<title>Upper Mustang Trek</title>
	<link>https://pudirectory.com/travel-agencies/690-upper-mustang-trek</link>
	<description><![CDATA[Upper Mustang Trek is a standout amongst the most interesting encounters that you can have in Nepal. Culture and way of life of individuals Upper Mustang or Lo Manthang take after to that of Tibet and the territory is home to antiquated expressions and religious communities going back to numerous hundreds of years.Trek to the current region is thru unproductive, nearly untimbered landscapes, sturdy winds typically scream across the world in the afternoon, generally, quiet down at the hours of darkness. Being within the area space of mountain range has less downfall than the remaining components of Kingdom of Nepal.]]></description>
	<dc:creator>superadmin</dc:creator>
	<pubDate>Sun, 26 Nov 2017 08:25:35 +0100</pubDate>
	<guid>https://pudirectory.com/travel-agencies/690-upper-mustang-trek</guid>
</item>
<item>
	<title>Welcome Nepal Treks &amp; Tours</title>
	<link>https://pudirectory.com/travel-agencies/683-welcome-nepal-treks-tours</link>
	<description><![CDATA[We are professional Nepal Tour Company, Tour in Nepal with Nepal Travel Agency. Nepal Tour Company Committed Best service reasonable rate guaranteed!]]></description>
	<dc:creator>superadmin</dc:creator>
	<pubDate>Sun, 19 Nov 2017 03:56:50 +0100</pubDate>
	<guid>https://pudirectory.com/travel-agencies/683-welcome-nepal-treks-tours</guid>
</item>
<item>
	<title>Mardi Himal Trek</title>
	<link>https://pudirectory.com/travel-agencies/682-mardi-himal-trek</link>
	<description><![CDATA[Mardi Himal Trek is the most brief and best grand trail to achieve the base of the Mountain. Amid the trek, there is no opportunity to squint your eyes. While trekking the perspectives of Annapurna, Dhaulagiri, Machhapuchhre and Manaslu Himalaya come's in front to you. The Mardi Himal Trek was opened to vacationer in 2012. ]]></description>
	<dc:creator>superadmin</dc:creator>
	<pubDate>Thu, 16 Nov 2017 06:14:30 +0100</pubDate>
	<guid>https://pudirectory.com/travel-agencies/682-mardi-himal-trek</guid>
</item>
<item>
	<title>Asian Journey Pvt Ltd</title>
	<link>https://pudirectory.com/travel-agencies/681-asian-journey-pvt-ltd</link>
	<description><![CDATA[Asian Journeys Pvt Ltd – is a privately owned adventure outfitting company that specializes in providing our clients with high-level experiences in the Himalayas. Founded in Nepal in 2003 we have more than 12 years of experience in providing our clients with life long memories of Trekking in the Himalayas. We from the depth of heart would like to provide a comfort with thrilling adventures to our clients and also some of the notable qualities to provide to you are:

We offer outdoor adventure trips into three very different cultures that include Nepal, Bhutan and Tibet.
We provide you with trips that include peak climbing, mountaineering, rafting, mountain biking as well as wildlife safaris. also providing cultural toursas well.
We will be happy to develop a custom tour that will meet all of the requests of our clients.
We can mix or match activities as needed to exceed your expectations during your time with our friendly and experienced guides.
We can also address any special physical or dining requirements. Think of us when planning your honeymoon, or photography adventures.
Our team is a group of experts who have academic and technical expertise in the tourism industry and our company has got a collective experience of more than a decade. Our loyal, committed and experienced staff gives us the edge over our competition. Our motto “Safety, comfort and standard service in the price you can afford” reflects the wide range of services we provide to our valued customers.

Our Tour leaders and guide who are a specialist in religion, culture, and tradition in this region has helped a lot to establish our company as the leading trek organizers in the region in a short span of time.

We are committed to provide personalized services to our clients even before they leave home and until they are back home sound and safe. Our team provides sound knowledge of health issues, trek preparations, visa and other frontier formalities and other many issues related to travelling.

If you have a passion for travel and want to experience the ultimate adventure in Himalayan region (Nepal, Tibet, Bhutan & India), then you can entrust us. With the better understanding of your desire to visit new places and come home with a real sense of satisfaction, we have the potential to turn your dream adventure trip into a reality while taking care of your interest.]]></description>
	<dc:creator>superadmin</dc:creator>
	<pubDate>Wed, 15 Nov 2017 01:56:48 +0100</pubDate>
	<guid>https://pudirectory.com/travel-agencies/681-asian-journey-pvt-ltd</guid>
</item>
<item>
	<title>Welcome Nepal Treks &amp; Tours</title>
	<link>https://pudirectory.com/travel-agencies/680-welcome-nepal-treks-tours</link>
	<description><![CDATA[We are professional Nepal Tour Company, Tour in Nepal with Nepal Travel Agency. Nepal Tour Company Committed Best service reasonable rate guaranteed!]]></description>
	<dc:creator>superadmin</dc:creator>
	<pubDate>Mon, 13 Nov 2017 08:01:11 +0100</pubDate>
	<guid>https://pudirectory.com/travel-agencies/680-welcome-nepal-treks-tours</guid>
</item>
<item>
	<title>Annapurna Base Camp Trek</title>
	<link>https://pudirectory.com/travel-agencies/678-annapurna-base-camp-trek</link>
	<description><![CDATA[Annapurna Base Camp Trek or first rudiment trek is thus notable trekking destination around trekkers. whereas you complete Annapurna Base camp trek you may step to end one,475,890 Stairs. we'll begin the trek with less crowed and natural scenic half Khoramukh. 
The Annapurna Base Camp Trek offers a chance to induce too high Himalayan altitudes wherever glaciers replace rivers. One should ascend the foothills from Pokhara, appreciating the slate-roofed tropical villages and luxurious bush forests, gorges, etc., and once we climb higher, we are going to get to the hidden world of the Annapurna Sanctuary.
]]></description>
	<dc:creator>superadmin</dc:creator>
	<pubDate>Thu, 09 Nov 2017 08:07:09 +0100</pubDate>
	<guid>https://pudirectory.com/travel-agencies/678-annapurna-base-camp-trek</guid>
</item>
<item>
	<title>Welcome Nepal Treks &amp; Tours</title>
	<link>https://pudirectory.com/travel-agencies/672-welcome-nepal-treks-tours</link>
	<description><![CDATA[We are professional Nepal Tour Company, Tour in Nepal with Nepal Travel Agency. Nepal Tour Company Committed Best service reasonable rate guaranteed!
https://www.nepaltourstravel.com/
]]></description>
	<dc:creator>superadmin</dc:creator>
	<pubDate>Wed, 08 Nov 2017 08:37:19 +0100</pubDate>
	<guid>https://pudirectory.com/travel-agencies/672-welcome-nepal-treks-tours</guid>
</item>
<item>
	<title>Adventure Thirdpole Treks and Expedition Pvt. Ltd</title>
	<link>https://pudirectory.com/travel-agencies/653-adventure-thirdpole-treks-and-expedition-pvt-ltd</link>
	<description><![CDATA[ Adventure Thirdpole treks and Expedition is one of the best trekking company in Nepal. Based In kathmandu. We operates trekking, tours, adventure and expedition .]]></description>
	<dc:creator>superadmin</dc:creator>
	<pubDate>Thu, 26 Oct 2017 04:10:16 +0100</pubDate>
	<guid>https://pudirectory.com/travel-agencies/653-adventure-thirdpole-treks-and-expedition-pvt-ltd</guid>
</item>
<item>
	<title>Himalayan Smile Treks</title>
	<link>https://pudirectory.com/travel-agencies/647-himalayan-smile-treks</link>
	<description><![CDATA[ Himalayan Smile treks and Adventure - one of the leading trekking company in Nepal. Organizes the tourism products and services like trekking, hiking, wildlife adventure and tours.....]]></description>
	<dc:creator>superadmin</dc:creator>
	<pubDate>Tue, 10 Oct 2017 09:00:06 +0100</pubDate>
	<guid>https://pudirectory.com/travel-agencies/647-himalayan-smile-treks</guid>
</item>
<item>
	<title>Nepal Trekking Tourism &amp; Adventure</title>
	<link>https://pudirectory.com/travel-agencies/646-nepal-trekking-tourism-adventure</link>
	<description><![CDATA[Mount Everest, Nepal Trekking Tourism & Adventure (NTTA) is a Professional and dedicated Nepal based local trekking & Touring Company. Nepal Trekking Tourism & Adventure is run under the leadership of Pasang Sherpa, who has 20 years of most successful collective experience in the field of Nepalese Tourism, is also known as successful Sherpa tourism entrepreneur of Nepal. Nepal Trekking Tourism & Adventure is officially registered and authorized by Government of Nepal, Nepal Tourism Board and all tourism related Associations of Nepal Government. Nepal Trekking Tourism & Adventure (NTTA) aims to Provide top Quality trekking & touring services in Nepal for all trekkers.]]></description>
	<dc:creator>superadmin</dc:creator>
	<pubDate>Tue, 10 Oct 2017 03:37:32 +0100</pubDate>
	<guid>https://pudirectory.com/travel-agencies/646-nepal-trekking-tourism-adventure</guid>
</item>
<item>
	<title>Achyut Dahal</title>
	<link>https://pudirectory.com/travel-agencies/638-achyut-dahal</link>
	<description><![CDATA[Global Link Tours & Travel is formed by a team of experienced and well-qualified staff who have been working for several years in the  field of Tourism. Each of our team members is very knowledgeable about the countries in which we lead tours. We are proud to mention that our strong relationships and networks throughout Nepal, Tibet, Bhutan and India as well as our understanding of the cultural nuances, ensure that each trip provides clients with the highest level of personal satisfaction in every aspects.

Global Link Tours & Travel is a Budget Tour Operator for Nepal, Tibet, Bhutan and India specializing in Adventure Trekking, Leisure Tours, Pilgrimage Tours and other Adventure Trips for clients interested in all the different destinations.]]></description>
	<dc:creator>superadmin</dc:creator>
	<pubDate>Sun, 24 Sep 2017 06:55:57 +0100</pubDate>
	<guid>https://pudirectory.com/travel-agencies/638-achyut-dahal</guid>
</item>
<item>
	<title>Duke Nepal</title>
	<link>https://pudirectory.com/travel-agencies/633-duke-nepal</link>
	<description><![CDATA[Duke Nepal Adventure is the best operator of Ghandruk trekking package as our package is economic &amp; enjoyable too &amp; it is the easiest trek of Nepal. Join us

Ghorepani Poonhill Trekking
Ghorepani Poonhill Trekking;An Easy Trek

Ghorepani Poonhill Trekking is a popular trekking route among Nepalese and foreigners too. It is a short and easy adventure around Annapurna region where any individual can have once in a lifetime memories. Stunning Sunrise view , the  panorama of Himalayas, natural and cultural importance of  place makes this trek extra beautiful. Poonhill view point offers rich view of Annapurna, Dhaulagiri, Nilgiri, Himchuli, Machhapuchre and other Himalaya peaks. Gurungs and Magars are local inhabitants of Ghorepani and this place also offers cultural insight of these communities.
]]></description>
	<dc:creator>superadmin</dc:creator>
	<pubDate>Mon, 18 Sep 2017 06:27:19 +0100</pubDate>
	<guid>https://pudirectory.com/travel-agencies/633-duke-nepal</guid>
</item>
<item>
	<title>Nepalmakalu</title>
	<link>https://pudirectory.com/travel-agencies/623-nepalmakalu</link>
	<description><![CDATA[We are a registered adventure tour company operating since 1998 from Kathmandu, Nepal. We run tours and treks in the Himalayan regions of Nepal, Tibet, Bhutan, and India with a highly rated reputation forquality, friendly professionalism and safety with a high client return rate.]]></description>
	<dc:creator>superadmin</dc:creator>
	<pubDate>Mon, 11 Sep 2017 03:39:53 +0100</pubDate>
	<guid>https://pudirectory.com/travel-agencies/623-nepalmakalu</guid>
</item>
<item>
	<title>Global Link Tours &amp; Travel</title>
	<link>https://pudirectory.com/travel-agencies/610-global-link-tours-travel</link>
	<description><![CDATA[<img align="right" src="https://pudirectory.com/media/com_mtree/images/listings/s/382.jpg" alt="Global Link Tours & Travel" />Global Link Tours & Travel is a Budget Tour Operator for Nepal and service oriented trekking agency based in Nepal, specializing for Trekking in Nepal.
]]></description>
	<dc:creator>superadmin</dc:creator>
	<pubDate>Sun, 03 Sep 2017 07:38:25 +0100</pubDate>
	<guid>https://pudirectory.com/travel-agencies/610-global-link-tours-travel</guid>
</item>
<item>
	<title>Blossom Expeditions Pvt. Ltd.</title>
	<link>https://pudirectory.com/travel-agencies/608-blossom-expeditions-pvt-ltd</link>
	<description><![CDATA[Whether you want adventerous moment and guidance in thinking about your next adventure or need help with an existing booking, our Blossom Expeditions are on hand. Talk to us for travel advice on 977 - 9841454462 in Nepal and 415-694-1388 in USA.
]]></description>
	<dc:creator>superadmin</dc:creator>
	<pubDate>Fri, 01 Sep 2017 15:50:51 +0100</pubDate>
	<guid>https://pudirectory.com/travel-agencies/608-blossom-expeditions-pvt-ltd</guid>
</item>
<item>
	<title>Nepal Trekking-Nepal Peak Climbing-Nepal Pilgrimage Tours</title>
	<link>https://pudirectory.com/travel-agencies/606-nepal-trekking-nepal-peak-climbing-nepal-pilgrimage-tours</link>
	<description><![CDATA[<img align="right" src="https://pudirectory.com/media/com_mtree/images/listings/s/381.jpg" alt="Nepal Trekking-Nepal Peak Climbing-Nepal Pilgrimage Tours" />Blossom Expeditions is a tour, trekking and outdoor company based in Nepal. We have specialized Trekking, Climbing,  Pilgrimage Tours and Exploring off the Beaten Tracks.
]]></description>
	<dc:creator>superadmin</dc:creator>
	<pubDate>Thu, 31 Aug 2017 15:41:44 +0100</pubDate>
	<guid>https://pudirectory.com/travel-agencies/606-nepal-trekking-nepal-peak-climbing-nepal-pilgrimage-tours</guid>
</item>
<item>
	<title>Hom Ramdam</title>
	<link>https://pudirectory.com/travel-agencies/602-hom-ramdam</link>
	<description><![CDATA[<img align="right" src="https://pudirectory.com/media/com_mtree/images/listings/s/380.jpg" alt="Hom Ramdam" />Tourist Link Trek is an eco friendly trekking and travel Company based in the Himalayan country of Nepal. We have been working in the tourism of Nepal since many years. We had spent a life time Trekking, Peak Climbing, Expedition, Mountaineering, Day Hiking, Sightseeing, Wildlife safari adventure tour as well as Tibet and Bhutan tour. Our company runs by a group experienced, knowledgeable and experience guide team of Nepal. If you do trip with us defiantly your trip will comfortable, safety and Memorable.]]></description>
	<dc:creator>superadmin</dc:creator>
	<pubDate>Tue, 29 Aug 2017 09:04:11 +0100</pubDate>
	<guid>https://pudirectory.com/travel-agencies/602-hom-ramdam</guid>
</item>
<item>
	<title>Nepal Trekking</title>
	<link>https://pudirectory.com/travel-agencies/601-nepal-trekking</link>
	<description><![CDATA[Trekking in Nepal is the only way to experiences the world best and exotic, unique cultures, traditions, local lifestyle and thrilling beauty of the mightiest Himalayas.  Nepal Himalayas offers ultimate opportunities to explore stunning mountains views with beautiful floras and faunas.]]></description>
	<dc:creator>superadmin</dc:creator>
	<pubDate>Mon, 28 Aug 2017 11:09:47 +0100</pubDate>
	<guid>https://pudirectory.com/travel-agencies/601-nepal-trekking</guid>
</item>
<item>
	<title>Himalayan Asia Treks and Expedition P. Ltd.</title>
	<link>https://pudirectory.com/travel-agencies/580-himalayan-asia-treks-and-expedition-p-ltd</link>
	<description><![CDATA[Himalayan Asia Treks is local Trekking Agency in Nepal. We organize Nepal Trekking, Trekking in Nepal, Nepal Treks, Trek in Nepal, Trekking Nepal.]]></description>
	<dc:creator>superadmin</dc:creator>
	<pubDate>Wed, 26 Jul 2017 12:34:31 +0100</pubDate>
	<guid>https://pudirectory.com/travel-agencies/580-himalayan-asia-treks-and-expedition-p-ltd</guid>
</item>
<item>
	<title>Nepal Base Camp Treks Pvt. Ltd.</title>
	<link>https://pudirectory.com/travel-agencies/571-nepal-base-camp-treks-pvt-ltd</link>
	<description><![CDATA[<img align="right" src="https://pudirectory.com/media/com_mtree/images/listings/s/350.jpg" alt="Nepal Base Camp Treks Pvt. Ltd." />For over a decade now, Nepal Base Camp Treks have been the preferred choice for trekking enthusiasts, hiking the entirety of Nepal’s stunning Himalayas. Operated by highly experienced trek planners, the company has been guiding trekkers through one of the most beautiful mountain terrains in the world. But it’s not just trekking in Nepal that the company has expertise in; it also arranges yoga, slide shows, cultural tours, short hiking, bird watching, etc.

Treks we arrange

•  Annapurna region trekking
•  Langtang region trekking
•  Wilderness trekking
•  Everest region trekking
•  Ghale Gaun trek
•  Mardi Himal trek

Tours we arrange

•  Chitwan jungle safari 
•  Kathmandu Nagarkot Dhulikhel tour
•  Helicopter tour in Nepal
•  Nepal Widlife Safari
•  Mountain flight in Nepal
•  Mountain Biking in Nepal
•  Paragliding in Nepal

Mission

Our mission has always been to give you an amazing cultural experience which is filled with culturally enriching adventures in Everest base camp trekking. Not just in Nepal, but we also operate treks and tours in India, Tibet and Bhutan. We understand the fact that you work hard all year to make your dream travel a reality and the fact that you want to travel with a purpose. Precisely for this reason, we go the extra mile in ensuring that your trip is meaningful. Through excellent services, we aim to offer you value for money trip packages at best prices.]]></description>
	<dc:creator>superadmin</dc:creator>
	<pubDate>Tue, 11 Jul 2017 09:33:34 +0100</pubDate>
	<guid>https://pudirectory.com/travel-agencies/571-nepal-base-camp-treks-pvt-ltd</guid>
</item>
<item>
	<title>Sujan Sitaula</title>
	<link>https://pudirectory.com/travel-agencies/560-sujan-sitaula</link>
	<description><![CDATA[Beside the Himalayan Treks and Expedition is an well equipped, trustworthy and highly experienced trekking and tour agency in Nepal, authorized by Nepal Government with all local crews. We specealize for Trekking in Nepal, Nepal Adventure Holidays and other exciting outdoor activities. Our Trekking Company has been launched by a professional and energetic team after gaining deep knowledge and more than a decade blend experience in tourism industry. Our professional management, expert guides, familiar staffs are the sources for Himalayan fun and adventure. We proudly as well as perfectly organize exciting treks, classic and scenic tour, peak climbing, rafting, jungle safari, expedition, paragliding, bungee jump, mountain flight, hiking, sightseeing and other adventurous activities with best price and excellent service guarantee to make your vacation lifetime unforgettable. Our service is extended to Bhutan and Tibet as well. We are an excellent service provider in any outdoor activities either directly touched our valued clients or through our partnership agencies throughout the world. We are also extending our service coordinating with agencies and related travel crews. We are very satisfied from our every client after the response of our every program and till now we never heard even one weak points of our company, of our management and of our staffs. We have succeeded to print our organized activities in their mind as lifetime memorable, which is our goal.]]></description>
	<dc:creator>superadmin</dc:creator>
	<pubDate>Sun, 25 Jun 2017 02:27:17 +0100</pubDate>
	<guid>https://pudirectory.com/travel-agencies/560-sujan-sitaula</guid>
</item>
</channel>
</rss>
