<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/" xmlns:mtree="http://www.mosets.com/tree/rss/">
<channel>
<title>Purbanchal Directory - Recently Added Listings - Shopping</title>
<description></description>
<link>https://pudirectory.com/</link>
<lastBuildDate>Sat, 25 Apr 2020 13:29:59 +0100</lastBuildDate>
<generator>FeedCreator 1.7.3</generator>
<item>
	<title>Quality Sport - Custom Sports Apparel</title>
	<link>https://pudirectory.com/shopping/3455-quality-sport-custom-sports-apparel</link>
	<description><![CDATA[Quality Sport LTD mission is for you to be happy with not only our product but the entire ordering and communication process. We are certain you will be as excited as we are to push the limits with quality sport. We’ve been producing custom clothing for over 41 years, and our experience is evident in everything that we do. Choose quality sport as your custom sports apparel. We have a team of talented designers to help bring your vision to reality. Customized embroidered patches, heat seal, Silk-Screen, Sublimation, Tackle Twill for your Sports Team Uniforms/Clothes/Apparels. Call 514.934.6099 today and get a quote now!
]]></description>
	<dc:creator>superadmin</dc:creator>
	<pubDate>Tue, 21 Apr 2020 07:07:06 +0100</pubDate>
	<guid>https://pudirectory.com/shopping/3455-quality-sport-custom-sports-apparel</guid>
</item>
<item>
	<title>Central Mall</title>
	<link>https://pudirectory.com/shopping/1400-central-mall</link>
	<description><![CDATA[<img align="right" src="https://pudirectory.com/media/com_mtree/images/listings/s/538.jpg" alt="Central Mall" />In order to bring back the Glory of the City, 3 prominent business houses, Debenara Group, Vishal group, and Hi-Life group joined hands to develop an International Standard Mall and Multiplex at the Heart of the Biratnagar City, and named it Central Mall, Central Multiplex. Central Mall is designed as the retail redefinition of Biratnagar, an International Standard of shopping & entertainment destination with a built up area of 1 Lakh 34 thousand square feet.

 

Central Mall is the first premium retail & entertainment destination mall in Biratnagar. It has been designed to complement the changing perspectives and lifestyles of modern-day Biratnagar with state-of-the-art building systems and a superior design balancing the contemporary architecture. It stands as a symbol of positive growth and it is a Multi-utility commercial complex comprising a wide range of luxury Brand Outlets, Department Store, Food Court, Entertainment Zones, 2-Screen Multiplex and Sky lounge & Bar – all come together in the upmarket Main road -7 to offer the epitome of Hospitality not just in Birat but in the state no.1.Central Mall has earned the Destination of being the City's only organized Fashion Destination.
]]></description>
	<dc:creator>superadmin</dc:creator>
	<pubDate>Mon, 08 Apr 2019 13:49:14 +0100</pubDate>
	<guid>https://pudirectory.com/shopping/1400-central-mall</guid>
</item>
<item>
	<title>Oldpinch Online Shopping</title>
	<link>https://pudirectory.com/shopping/949-oldpinch-online-shopping</link>
	<description><![CDATA[<img align="right" src="https://pudirectory.com/media/com_mtree/images/listings/s/458.jpg" alt="Oldpinch Online Shopping" />eCommerce website https://www.oldpinch.com which sells various electronic products and cosmetic products at very reasonable price.Free home delivery inside Kathmandu and delivery all over Nepal. Quality products at very best prices. Easy Return policies and own ware house.]]></description>
	<dc:creator>superadmin</dc:creator>
	<pubDate>Thu, 14 Jun 2018 08:30:21 +0100</pubDate>
	<guid>https://pudirectory.com/shopping/949-oldpinch-online-shopping</guid>
</item>
<item>
	<title>SmartDoko - One Click Solution</title>
	<link>https://pudirectory.com/shopping/935-smartdoko-one-click-solution</link>
	<description><![CDATA[<img align="right" src="https://pudirectory.com/media/com_mtree/images/listings/s/452.jpg" alt="SmartDoko - One Click Solution" />SmartDoko is an online shopping destination in Nepal offering the wide range of products whereby the customers can enjoy a hassle-free purchase of products which is now just a click away from reaching to their doorsteps.]]></description>
	<dc:creator>superadmin</dc:creator>
	<pubDate>Fri, 01 Jun 2018 05:17:44 +0100</pubDate>
	<guid>https://pudirectory.com/shopping/935-smartdoko-one-click-solution</guid>
</item>
</channel>
</rss>
