<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/" xmlns:mtree="http://www.mosets.com/tree/rss/">
<channel>
<title>Purbanchal Directory - Recently Added Listings - ISP</title>
<description></description>
<link>https://pudirectory.com/</link>
<lastBuildDate>Sat, 25 Apr 2020 13:28:14 +0100</lastBuildDate>
<generator>FeedCreator 1.7.3</generator>
<item>
	<title>Websurfer Nepal Communication System Pvt. Ltd.</title>
	<link>https://pudirectory.com/isp/357-websurfer-nepal-communication-system-pvt-ltd</link>
	<description><![CDATA[
It was founded in January 2001 by a young computer literate who made his aim on 1992 and joint venture with a successful businessman Mr. K T Vimalanathan, from United Kingdom who was graduated from Imperial College London in UK. Mr. Vimalanathan made his fortune in Internet businesses in the early age of the Internet. Company CEO and Founder Mr. Vimalanathan has successful portfolio by floating Internet Company in FTSE100.

After a flourishing step toward the cutting edge technology Websurfer has formed the technology research and development department where the entire engineers research about the cutting edge technology and provide the stable and affordable products to entire Nepal.

After the winning research and implementation on wireless internet, now Websurfer Nepal also has fiber optic cable internet around the Kathmandu Valley. Company also provides VSAT Networks, Dialup Internet, Cable Internet, Wireless Hotspots, Wireless Internet and Web Hosting

Company chairman Mr. S. Chhetri strongly believes that company has a unique and open approach and has created the business model required by client. We believe on providing the new and affordable products to our customers and we depend on their success.

--------------------------------------

Bhola Katwal
Business Associate
Websurfer Nepal Communication System Pvt. Ltd.
Rangeli Road, Biratnagar, Nepal
Tel.: 021-533087
Mobile: 9842246380
Email: biratnagar@wsn.com.np
Web: www.websurfer.com.np]]></description>
	<dc:creator>superadmin</dc:creator>
	<pubDate>Thu, 02 Mar 2017 05:06:11 +0100</pubDate>
	<guid>https://pudirectory.com/isp/357-websurfer-nepal-communication-system-pvt-ltd</guid>
</item>
<item>
	<title>SUBISU Cablenet Pvt. Ltd.</title>
	<link>https://pudirectory.com/isp/356-subisu-cablenet-pvt-ltd</link>
	<description><![CDATA[
Subisu Group has a diversified operation in the field of Trading, Cable TV and Cable Internet services. Subisu Cablenet Pvt. Ltd. was established in 1999 and provides internet through it's existing HFC network along with 75 TV channels both free to air and pay channels providing avenues of entertainment for the people of Kathmandu. Subisu Cablenet is the first and the only cable Internet service provider and the only cable operator in Nepal to be certified ISO 9001:2000. Cable connections are considered as one of the best types of Internet connection available to the Internet users; they offer fast and reliable connections.

----------------------------------------------
Address
148 Thirbum Sadak, Baluwatar Kathmandu, Nepal
Phone: + 977 1 4429616, 4429617
Fax: + 977-01-4430572

Traffic Chowk, Biratnagar, Nepal
Phone: 021-440438
Cell: 9742073624

Email: info@subisu.net.np
Website: http://www.subisu.net.np]]></description>
	<dc:creator>superadmin</dc:creator>
	<pubDate>Thu, 02 Mar 2017 05:04:26 +0100</pubDate>
	<guid>https://pudirectory.com/isp/356-subisu-cablenet-pvt-ltd</guid>
</item>
<item>
	<title>Nepal Telecom, Nepal Doorsanchar Company Limited</title>
	<link>https://pudirectory.com/isp/355-nepal-telecom-nepal-doorsanchar-company-limited</link>
	<description><![CDATA[Nepal Telecom, Nepal Doorsanchar Company Limited
Mission
"Nepal Telecom as a progressive, customer spirited and consumer responsive Entity is committed to provide nation-wide reliable telecommunication service to serve as an impetus to the social, political and economic development of the Country"

Vision
"Vision of Nepal Telecom is to remain a dominant player in telecommunication sector in the Country while also extending reliable and cost effective services to all"

Goal
"Goal of Nepal Telecom is to provide cost effective telecommunication services to every nook and corner of country"

------------------------------------------

Telecom Office, Beltar
Beltar, Udayapur
Phone:
035-440111 (Office Incharge)

Telecom Office, Bhadrapur
Bhadrapur, Jhapa
Phone:
023-520444 (Office Incharge)
520185 (Revenue)
Fax: 520002

Telecom Office, Bhantabari
Bhantabari, Sunsari
Phone:
025-460000 (Office Incharge)
Telecom Office, Bhardaha
Bhardaha, Saptari
Phone:
031-440044 (Office Incharge)

Telecom Office, Bhojpur
Bhojpur, Bhojpur
Phone:
029-420222 (Office Incharge)
Fax: 420333

Telecom Office, Biratchauk
Biratchauk, Morang
Phone:
021-545444 (Office Incharge)
545111 (Sales)
545333 (Revenue)
Fax: 545222

Telecom Office, Biratnagar
Biratnagar, Morang
Phone:
021-528444 (Office Incharge)
527277 (Sales)
527787 (Revenue)
Fax: 525755

Telecom Office, Birtamod
Birtamod, Jhapa
Phone:
023-540444 (Office Incharge)
540333 (Sales)
540122 (Revenue)
Fax: 541444

Telecom Office, Budhabare
Budhabare, Jhapa
Phone:
023-555122 (Office Incharge)
Telecom Office, Chainpur
Chainpur, Sankhuwasabha
Phone:
029-570222 (Office Incharge)
570108 (Sales)
Fax: 570000

Telecom Office, Chandragadhi
Chandragadhi, Jhapa
Phone:
023-456534 (Office Incharge)

Telecom Office, Charaali
Charaali, Jhapa
Phone:
023-460222 (Office Incharge)
Telecom Office, Chatara
Chatara, Sunsari
Phone:
025-550144 (Office Incharge)

Telecom Office, Damak
Damak, Jhapa
Phone:
023-580444 (Office Incharge)
580888 (Sales)
580083 (Revenue)
Fax: 580543

Telecom Office, Dhangadhi
Dhangadhi, Siraha
Phone:
033-545144 (Office Incharge)
Telecom Office, Dhankuta
Dhankuta, Dhankuta
Phone:
026-520444 (Office Incharge)
520105 (Sales)
520105 (Revenue)
Fax: 520183

Telecom Office, Dharan
Dharan, Sunsari
Phone:
025-521444 (Office Incharge)
520001 (Sales)
520499 (Revenue)
Fax: 521777

Telecom Office, Dhulabari
Dhulabari, Jhapa
Phone:
023-560444 (Office Incharge)
560333 (Sales)
560600 (Revenue)
Fax: 560134
Telecom Office, Diktel
Diktel, Khotang
Phone:
036-420222 (Office Incharge)
Fax: 420101

Telecom Office, Duhabi
Duhabi, Morang
Phone:
025-540444 (Office Incharge)
540655 (Revenue)
Fax: 540555

Telecom Office, Fikkal
Fikkal, Ilam
Phone:
027-540444 (Office Incharge)
540101 (Sales)
Fax: 540333

Telecom Office, Gaighat
Gaighat, Udayapur
Phone:
035-420444 (Office Incharge)
420222 (Sales)
420555 (Revenue)]]></description>
	<dc:creator>superadmin</dc:creator>
	<pubDate>Thu, 02 Mar 2017 05:01:33 +0100</pubDate>
	<guid>https://pudirectory.com/isp/355-nepal-telecom-nepal-doorsanchar-company-limited</guid>
</item>
<item>
	<title>Mercantile Communications Pvt. Ltd.</title>
	<link>https://pudirectory.com/isp/354-mercantile-communications-pvt-ltd</link>
	<description><![CDATA[
Mercantile has been at the forefront of the Internet evolution and is a cutting edge Internet service provider (ISP) in Nepal. Mercantile pioneered the concept of providing Internet Service in Nepal when the popularity of Internet was just beginning in the United States of America. smarter Internet experience.

--------------------------------------------
Hiti Pokhari, Durbar Marg, Kathmandu, Nepal
P.O. Box: 876
Toll Free: 16600155555
Tel: 977-1-4445920 / 4440773
Fax: 977-1-4437088 / 4427614
Fax(Mc3): 977-1-4439360

Mahendra Chowk, Behind Nepal Bazar, Biratnagar

Cell: 9852028824/9842028824
Samuel Thapa
Branch Manager]]></description>
	<dc:creator>superadmin</dc:creator>
	<pubDate>Thu, 02 Mar 2017 04:59:20 +0100</pubDate>
	<guid>https://pudirectory.com/isp/354-mercantile-communications-pvt-ltd</guid>
</item>
<item>
	<title>Cyber World Pvt. Ltd.</title>
	<link>https://pudirectory.com/isp/353-cyber-world-pvt-ltd</link>
	<description><![CDATA[Cyber World Pvt. Ltd. ]]></description>
	<dc:creator>superadmin</dc:creator>
	<pubDate>Thu, 02 Mar 2017 04:56:52 +0100</pubDate>
	<guid>https://pudirectory.com/isp/353-cyber-world-pvt-ltd</guid>
</item>
<item>
	<title>Classic Tech Pvt. Ltd.</title>
	<link>https://pudirectory.com/isp/352-classic-tech-pvt-ltd</link>
	<description><![CDATA[Classic Tech Pvt. Ltd. ]]></description>
	<dc:creator>superadmin</dc:creator>
	<pubDate>Thu, 02 Mar 2017 04:55:46 +0100</pubDate>
	<guid>https://pudirectory.com/isp/352-classic-tech-pvt-ltd</guid>
</item>
<item>
	<title>WorldLink Communications P. Ltd</title>
	<link>https://pudirectory.com/isp/351-worldlink-communications-p-ltd</link>
	<description><![CDATA[<img align="right" src="https://pudirectory.com/media/com_mtree/images/listings/s/217.png" alt="WorldLink Communications P. Ltd" />WorldLink is the largest Internet Service Provider (ISP) in Nepal and one of the most prominent IT companies. Founded in September 1995 with the aim of providing Internet and IT services by its present Chairman and Managing Director, Dileep Agrawal, WorldLink started off by providing store-and-forward e-mail services over a dial-up link to the Internet in the US. In March 1997, WorldLink started providing full Internet access over a dedicated leased-line to the Internet backbone in the US through Teleglobe International. From September 1999 till June 2008, WorldLink has been connecting to the Internet over a direct satellite uplink through its own VSAT terminal, thereby completely bypassing Nepal Telecommunications Corporation, the local PTT, however now Worldlink owns International Private Leased Circuit (IPLC) network over undersea fiber to Singapore and peers directly with Singtel. Over the past 16 years, WorldLink has grown from a small business to a strong and stable corporation with professional staff and a strong customer base. The company has also positioned itself as a complete IT service provider rather than just an ISP, by providing services such as data connectivity, network integration and consulting, web hosting and development, hardware sales and maintenance, and software development and systems integration through its partnership with WorldLink Technologies Pvt Ltd. Our success as an excellent service provider is exemplified by the satisfaction of our customers, which include such reputed names as the United Nations, American Embassy and the Government of Nepal. WorldLink is a success story, the likes of which are usually found in the Silicon Valley. It has thus served as a role model for other startup IT companies. It has demonstrated to young entrepreneurs that IT is the wave of the future, even in a relatively small market like Nepal. It has undoubtedly contributed to the ongoing IT revolution visible in this small Himalayan country. In recognition of its contribution, Nepal Government has invited WorldLink to be a part of IT taskforces such as the National IT Infrastructure Development Committee and contribute to the development of IT in the country. ------------------------------------------------ WorldLink Communications P. Ltd. Jawalakhel Lalitpur P.O.Box 8207 Kathmandu, Nepal Fax: +977-1-5529403 Telephone: +977-1-5523050 Biratnagar Sansarimai Sthan, Main Road, Biratnagar -13 Phone : 021-530020 Email : info_brt@wlink.com.np Birtamod 2nd floor, Hanuman central, Mukti chowk, Anarmani – 3, Birtamode Tel : 023-544118 Email: info_btm@wlink.com.np Damak Damak-1, Khanal Market, Beldangiroad, Damak Tel : 023-584590 Email: info_dmk@wlink.com.np Dharan Tamu Complex, Bhanu Chowk Phone: 025-530900 E-mail: info_drn@wlink.com.np Itahari Itahari-11, Prabhamarg, Ithari Tel : 025-586616 Email: info_ith@wlink.com.np]]></description>
	<dc:creator>superadmin</dc:creator>
	<pubDate>Thu, 02 Mar 2017 04:52:53 +0100</pubDate>
	<guid>https://pudirectory.com/isp/351-worldlink-communications-p-ltd</guid>
</item>
</channel>
</rss>
