<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/" xmlns:mtree="http://www.mosets.com/tree/rss/">
<channel>
<title>Purbanchal Directory - Recently Added Listings - Tourist Attractions</title>
<description></description>
<link>https://pudirectory.com/</link>
<lastBuildDate>Sat, 25 Apr 2020 15:08:52 +0100</lastBuildDate>
<generator>FeedCreator 1.7.3</generator>
<item>
	<title>Nepal travel and trekking agency.</title>
	<link>https://pudirectory.com/tourist-attractions/626-nepal-travel-and-trekking-agency</link>
	<description><![CDATA[<img align="right" src="https://pudirectory.com/media/com_mtree/images/listings/s/393.jpg" alt="Nepal travel and trekking agency." />Trekking in Nepal After Earthquake has been declared as a safe trekking destination in Nepal. Following trekking regions are open now that you can enjoy the excursions in the Nepal Himalayas. Various temporary shelters have been re-established. Here are some popular trekking destinations, these are still open for your trekking plan in Nepal Himalayas. Please enjoy with following trekking and hiking area of Nepal.]]></description>
	<dc:creator>superadmin</dc:creator>
	<pubDate>Wed, 13 Sep 2017 02:19:03 +0100</pubDate>
	<guid>https://pudirectory.com/tourist-attractions/626-nepal-travel-and-trekking-agency</guid>
</item>
<item>
	<title>Eastern Tourism Development Organization</title>
	<link>https://pudirectory.com/tourist-attractions/192-eastern-tourism-development-organization</link>
	<description><![CDATA[Eastern Tourism Development Organization (पुर्वाञ्चल पर्यटन विकास संस्था)
पुर्वाञ्चल पर्यटन विकास संस्था प्रा.लि. हाम्रो देशको धार्मिक तथा पर्यटकीय क्षेत्रहरुको प्रचार प्रसार गर्न र सेवा मूलक लक्षयमा रहि हाम्रो देशमा पर्यटन विकासमा टेवा पु¥याउने उद्देश्यले नेपाल सरकार मार्फत रजिष्ट्रेशनको कार्यलय अन्र्तगत दर्ता गरी दर्ता नं. १२८८२२÷०७१÷०७२ र स्थायी लेखा नं. ६०२४३९१७६ अन्र्तगत संचालित एक संस्था हो]]></description>
	<dc:creator>superadmin</dc:creator>
	<pubDate>Fri, 24 Feb 2017 12:05:19 +0100</pubDate>
	<guid>https://pudirectory.com/tourist-attractions/192-eastern-tourism-development-organization</guid>
</item>
<item>
	<title>BHEDETAR</title>
	<link>https://pudirectory.com/tourist-attractions/191-bhedetar</link>
	<description><![CDATA[<img align="right" src="https://pudirectory.com/media/com_mtree/images/listings/s/142.jpg" alt="BHEDETAR" />
BHEDETAR
 
Altitude:  1420m
District: Sunsari
Zone: Koshi
Distance from Dharan: 16km north
Travel Options: Bus, Taxi]]></description>
	<dc:creator>superadmin</dc:creator>
	<pubDate>Fri, 24 Feb 2017 11:58:33 +0100</pubDate>
	<guid>https://pudirectory.com/tourist-attractions/191-bhedetar</guid>
</item>
<item>
	<title>Betana Wetland Area</title>
	<link>https://pudirectory.com/tourist-attractions/190-betana-wetland-area</link>
	<description><![CDATA[<img align="right" src="https://pudirectory.com/media/com_mtree/images/listings/s/137.jpg" alt="Betana Wetland Area" />
Two kilometers from Belbari is Betana Wetland Area, a serene wetland which is a popular picnic spot of Eastern Nepal. Located in the north of the Mahendra Highway, it is surrounded by green forests of tall SAAL Tree which fascinates anyone visiting here. On the other side of the road, there is a camp of tea stands loaded with junk food, tea, and varieties of soft drinks. Anyone would get the splendid forest view, when the still water reflect the trees, creating a double range.
Inside the Betana Wetland, there are several Kirati graveyards. The Kirati people (Kirat is a collective term for the Tibetan origin ethnic groups in eastern Nepal like Rai, Limbu, Lepcha, Dhimal etc) bury their dead and they put large tombstones with inscriptions. Thousands of visitors are attracted by its scenic view every year.
 
Amenities:
Includes picnic spot, boating, natural area, walkway – paved, trails – hiking, parking, restaurants)
 
Special Information:
Most visitors to the wetland can find themselves lucky if they get a glimpse of giant tortoise, varieties of birds, fresh water fishes and much more. Access to the wetland area is very easy. As an amenities there are several picnic spots, boating, parking area, restaurants and much more. There is specific fee for entrance, boating & Picnic. The entrance fee is Rs.5, Boating per group (up to 4 people for 30 minutes) is Rs.100 & Picnic spot fee is Rs.200 - Rs.300. This place is crowded during picnic seasons esp. Mangsir, Poush & Magh and New Year (Nepalese & English).
 
Bio-Diversity & Conversation Effort :
There is a rich bio-diversity in this wetland. If preserved, it can boost the tourism potential of Belbari & Eastern region. On the occasion of Belbari Festival observed last time, many political leaders, singers, artist and local tourists came to support and find out the possibilities of conserving this wetland, which will not only be a boom for the tourism, but will also protect the flora and fauna available here.

Follow the Link for You Tube Video:
http://www.youtube.com/watch?v=K157mvipWmo]]></description>
	<dc:creator>superadmin</dc:creator>
	<pubDate>Fri, 24 Feb 2017 11:50:56 +0100</pubDate>
	<guid>https://pudirectory.com/tourist-attractions/190-betana-wetland-area</guid>
</item>
</channel>
</rss>
