<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/" xmlns:mtree="http://www.mosets.com/tree/rss/">
<channel>
<title>Purbanchal Directory - Recently Updated Listings</title>
<description></description>
<link>https://pudirectory.com/</link>
<lastBuildDate>Sat, 25 Apr 2020 13:32:47 +0100</lastBuildDate>
<generator>FeedCreator 1.7.3</generator>
<item>
	<title>Quality Sport - Custom Sports Apparel</title>
	<link>https://pudirectory.com/shopping/3455-quality-sport-custom-sports-apparel</link>
	<description><![CDATA[Quality Sport LTD mission is for you to be happy with not only our product but the entire ordering and communication process. We are certain you will be as excited as we are to push the limits with quality sport. We’ve been producing custom clothing for over 41 years, and our experience is evident in everything that we do. Choose quality sport as your custom sports apparel. We have a team of talented designers to help bring your vision to reality. Customized embroidered patches, heat seal, Silk-Screen, Sublimation, Tackle Twill for your Sports Team Uniforms/Clothes/Apparels. Call 514.934.6099 today and get a quote now!
]]></description>
	<dc:creator>superadmin</dc:creator>
	<pubDate>Wed, 22 Apr 2020 07:59:01 +0100</pubDate>
	<guid>https://pudirectory.com/shopping/3455-quality-sport-custom-sports-apparel</guid>
</item>
<item>
	<title>EZ Name Change</title>
	<link>https://pudirectory.com/advertising-agencies/3457-ez-name-change</link>
	<description><![CDATA[California Name Change Service Agency. Name Change Specialists with FULL SERVICE.]]></description>
	<dc:creator>superadmin</dc:creator>
	<pubDate>Wed, 22 Apr 2020 07:58:06 +0100</pubDate>
	<guid>https://pudirectory.com/advertising-agencies/3457-ez-name-change</guid>
</item>
<item>
	<title>Office Furniture Warehouse of Miami</title>
	<link>https://pudirectory.com/furniture/3458-office-furniture-warehouse-of-miami</link>
	<description><![CDATA[Office Furniture Warehouse Of Miami has been servicing Miami and, Dade county all the way down to Homestead, Key Largo and Key West since 1990. We believe in providing excellent service, delivery and design at the lowest price point in the market. Our Miami location opens Monday through Friday from 9 AM to 6 PM and on Saturday by appointment only. Office Furniture Warehouse has been serving South Florida's businesses since 1990 and is the largest office furniture store in South Florida. We provide a large selection of in-stock, new and used office desks, chairs, tables and cubicles at very competitive prices. Aside from our competitive prices, we are able to deliver, install and fulfill your office furniture needs faster. For businesses residing in Miami-Dade county please visit our Miami showroom today]]></description>
	<dc:creator>superadmin</dc:creator>
	<pubDate>Wed, 22 Apr 2020 07:57:37 +0100</pubDate>
	<guid>https://pudirectory.com/furniture/3458-office-furniture-warehouse-of-miami</guid>
</item>
<item>
	<title>Auto Shop Pvt Ltd</title>
	<link>https://pudirectory.com/automobiles/496-earth-auto-wheels</link>
	<description><![CDATA[<img align="right" src="https://pudirectory.com/media/com_mtree/images/listings/s/423.png" alt="Auto Shop Pvt Ltd" />The products sold by Swaraj Mazda in Nepal are most demanded by the institutional sector like hospitals, schools and factories. Our buses and pickups are in high demand. We are the only company to sell small 4WDs in Nepal. Demand for our four wheel drive vehicles has also increased. These vehicles (4WD) are more in demand in areas like Humla, Jumla, Taplejung and other remote areas where other vehicles cannot reach with such ease.

Cummins Jakson Diesel Generators authorized dealer for Eastern part of Nepal.]]></description>
	<dc:creator>superadmin</dc:creator>
	<pubDate>Wed, 22 Apr 2020 07:49:38 +0100</pubDate>
	<guid>https://pudirectory.com/automobiles/496-earth-auto-wheels</guid>
</item>
<item>
	<title>Anjesh Koirala</title>
	<link>https://pudirectory.com/computers/3263-anjesh-koirala</link>
	<description><![CDATA[Contact me for any kind of IT solutions]]></description>
	<dc:creator>pdmt</dc:creator>
	<pubDate>Sun, 01 Mar 2020 11:06:56 +0100</pubDate>
	<guid>https://pudirectory.com/computers/3263-anjesh-koirala</guid>
</item>
<item>
	<title>Mero Vahan</title>
	<link>https://pudirectory.com/transportation/3246-mero-vahan</link>
	<description><![CDATA[<img align="right" src="https://pudirectory.com/media/com_mtree/images/listings/s/756.png" alt="Mero Vahan" />१.प्रयोग गर्न अत्यन्त सरल l
२.आफ्नै दरमा समान ढुवानी गर्न सकिने l
३.आफुले चाहेको सामान ढुवानी गर्न मिल्ने l
४. आफुले रोजेको शहर / नगरपालिकाहरुमा सामान ढुवानी गर्न सकिने l
५. अब सामान खोज्न भौतारिनु पर्दैन,कसैलाई भन्नु पर्दैन, सामान ढुवानी गर्ने अनुरोध स्वत: तपाईंको मोबाइलमा आउनेछ l 
६. राम्रो काम गरे बापत नगद पुरस्कार प्राप्त गर्न सकिने l 
७. आवश्यक भए फोनबाट समेत सहयोग प्राप्त गर्न सकिने l 
८. न्युनतम भुक्तानीको ग्यारेन्टी l
९. समान लिने र सामान झार्ने ठाउँमा गाडी पुग्नु भन्दा अगाडी स्वत:सूचना पुगिसकेकोले लोडिंग र अनलोडिंग गर्न समयको बचत 
१०. फुल लोड लिई सके लगेज लोड लिन सकिने l   ]]></description>
	<dc:creator>binay</dc:creator>
	<pubDate>Fri, 28 Feb 2020 06:31:38 +0100</pubDate>
	<guid>https://pudirectory.com/transportation/3246-mero-vahan</guid>
</item>
<item>
	<title>Hotel Pathibhara International Airport Taxi Service</title>
	<link>https://pudirectory.com/taxi/199-pathibhara-taxi-sewa</link>
	<description><![CDATA[<img align="right" src="https://pudirectory.com/media/com_mtree/images/listings/s/730.jpg" alt="Hotel Pathibhara International Airport Taxi Service" />Planning a trip to Itahari, Biratnagar, Dharan, Damak, Bhedetar, Dhankuta, Hile from airport of Biratnagar? Either alone, with the family or for business, don’t worry we’ve got you covered. We want you to enjoy what really matters and give you a stress-free travel experience wherever you are in the world, whether by taxi, train or bus. Simply search, book and Go! Just pick the date and call us and leave the rest with us. We only use the best partners in each destination to make sure you have not only the best rates but the best quality service! We have a mahindra's scorpio to pick and drop you  to promote Visit Nepal 2020.]]></description>
	<dc:creator>superadmin</dc:creator>
	<pubDate>Mon, 10 Feb 2020 10:49:28 +0100</pubDate>
	<guid>https://pudirectory.com/taxi/199-pathibhara-taxi-sewa</guid>
</item>
<item>
	<title>Grand Moving &amp; Storage</title>
	<link>https://pudirectory.com/transportation/2965-grand-moving-storage</link>
	<description><![CDATA[Piano movers also specializing in organs, antiques, grandfather clocks, safes, statues, hoisting, and high-end items. In addition, Grand Moving & Storage offers full service residential moving and climate controlled storage. We are licensed, bonded and insured with over 25 years of experience. We believe in providing experienced, honest, and trustworthy crews at an ethical price.]]></description>
	<dc:creator>superadmin</dc:creator>
	<pubDate>Wed, 22 Jan 2020 07:16:15 +0100</pubDate>
	<guid>https://pudirectory.com/transportation/2965-grand-moving-storage</guid>
</item>
<item>
	<title>Jean Bran</title>
	<link>https://pudirectory.com/financial-institutions/2960-jean-bran</link>
	<description><![CDATA[Our firm provides comprehensive financial services that are centered for your unique, needs, situations and personalities. We work every step of the way to assess your goals, understand your priorities, and create and develop long standing relations built on trust.]]></description>
	<dc:creator>superadmin</dc:creator>
	<pubDate>Tue, 21 Jan 2020 15:39:12 +0100</pubDate>
	<guid>https://pudirectory.com/financial-institutions/2960-jean-bran</guid>
</item>
<item>
	<title>Premier Paradise, Inc</title>
	<link>https://pudirectory.com/manufacturing-industries/2959-premier-paradise-inc</link>
	<description><![CDATA[Founded in 2009, Premier Paradise provides innovative design and expert construction of custom swimming pools, watershapes, and luxury outdoor environments. Whether it’s modern, transitional or traditional, we create pools, spas, water features and landscaping along with cabanas, fireplaces, outdoor kitchens, and living areas that enhance your lifestyle.]]></description>
	<dc:creator>superadmin</dc:creator>
	<pubDate>Tue, 21 Jan 2020 15:38:07 +0100</pubDate>
	<guid>https://pudirectory.com/manufacturing-industries/2959-premier-paradise-inc</guid>
</item>
<item>
	<title>Hotel Suravi</title>
	<link>https://pudirectory.com/hotels/527-hotel-suravi</link>
	<description><![CDATA[<img align="right" src="https://pudirectory.com/media/com_mtree/images/listings/s/307.jpg" alt="Hotel Suravi" />Thinking about holiday? Dhankuta is the headquarter of Koshi Zone, Nepal. Hotel Suravi is situated at the heard of the city. One of the oldest hospitality business of the town is one of the best Hotels at Dhankuta, Nepal. Known for its friendly staffs and good foods you will mesmerize and cherish the stay at our hotel. Our well furnished rooms as well as clean bed sheet will certainly add value to your stay.
The natural hills and scenic beauty will make you forget about the chaos of the city and traffic jams. Dhankuta is known for the greenery as well as temples and ethnic foods. The food lovers will definitely enjoy our varieties offered.]]></description>
	<dc:creator>superadmin</dc:creator>
	<pubDate>Mon, 20 Jan 2020 06:29:04 +0100</pubDate>
	<guid>https://pudirectory.com/hotels/527-hotel-suravi</guid>
</item>
<item>
	<title>New Airport Taxi Service</title>
	<link>https://pudirectory.com/taxi/2932-new-airport-taxi-service</link>
	<description><![CDATA[<img align="right" src="https://pudirectory.com/media/com_mtree/images/listings/s/698.jpg" alt="New Airport Taxi Service" />We are the best airport taxi service provider from Biratnagar and nearby areas. You can call us for booking vehicles such as scorpio, bolero, maruti etc.
 
Call us at 9843767704
Ramesh Sitaula
Itahari]]></description>
	<dc:creator>superadmin</dc:creator>
	<pubDate>Mon, 20 Jan 2020 03:52:55 +0100</pubDate>
	<guid>https://pudirectory.com/taxi/2932-new-airport-taxi-service</guid>
</item>
<item>
	<title>Ronak Traders</title>
	<link>https://pudirectory.com/drinking-water/2845-ronak-traders</link>
	<description><![CDATA[<img align="right" src="https://pudirectory.com/media/com_mtree/images/listings/s/681.jpg" alt="Ronak Traders" />We deal with Aqua sales and also provide service for water purifiers. We have all spare parts available here. Our service area ranges from school to hospital and offices to industrial area. 

Specification  - Deals in all types of RO's, Aqua Guard, and water filters with UV  and TDS controllers.. Assures  1 year guarantee with  servicing. 

Products : sediment  filters, analogue  filters, specially  deals with  blue mount  filters  and  RO's .

Mobile - 9805354592
              9804006543]]></description>
	<dc:creator>superadmin</dc:creator>
	<pubDate>Mon, 06 Jan 2020 06:35:39 +0100</pubDate>
	<guid>https://pudirectory.com/drinking-water/2845-ronak-traders</guid>
</item>
<item>
	<title>Just Dining Chairs</title>
	<link>https://pudirectory.com/furniture/962-just-dining-chairs</link>
	<description><![CDATA[Just Dining Chairs is an Australian retailer dedicated to offering a wide range of quality products, conveniently delivering them straight to-your-door and providing an exceptional online shopping experience.
]]></description>
	<dc:creator>superadmin</dc:creator>
	<pubDate>Mon, 06 Jan 2020 06:24:40 +0100</pubDate>
	<guid>https://pudirectory.com/furniture/962-just-dining-chairs</guid>
</item>
<item>
	<title>MB Technology</title>
	<link>https://pudirectory.com/electronics/2766-mb-technology</link>
	<description><![CDATA[We provides all kinds of electronic accessories...]]></description>
	<dc:creator>prakash</dc:creator>
	<pubDate>Mon, 23 Dec 2019 10:22:29 +0100</pubDate>
	<guid>https://pudirectory.com/electronics/2766-mb-technology</guid>
</item>
<item>
	<title>HasgTag Food &amp; Bar</title>
	<link>https://pudirectory.com/restaurants/2765-hasgtag-food-bar</link>
	<description><![CDATA[<img align="right" src="https://pudirectory.com/media/com_mtree/images/listings/s/656.jpg" alt="HasgTag Food & Bar" />Best and tasty food in Biratnagar, with live music...]]></description>
	<dc:creator>prakash</dc:creator>
	<pubDate>Mon, 23 Dec 2019 10:08:27 +0100</pubDate>
	<guid>https://pudirectory.com/restaurants/2765-hasgtag-food-bar</guid>
</item>
<item>
	<title>HashTag Food &amp; Bar</title>
	<link>https://pudirectory.com/restaurants/2762-hashtag-food-bar</link>
	<description><![CDATA[Best and Tasty food in your demand with Live Music ,.....The place is decorated with natural beauty 
 and feel refreshed......]]></description>
	<dc:creator>prakash</dc:creator>
	<pubDate>Mon, 23 Dec 2019 09:21:17 +0100</pubDate>
	<guid>https://pudirectory.com/restaurants/2762-hashtag-food-bar</guid>
</item>
<item>
	<title>New Mahaveer Electricals</title>
	<link>https://pudirectory.com/electronics/2736-new-mahaveer-electricals</link>
	<description><![CDATA[<img align="right" src="https://pudirectory.com/media/com_mtree/images/listings/s/650.jpg" alt="New Mahaveer Electricals" />We are situated at Dharan Road Biratnagar. We are authorized distributors of Annapurna Enamelled Copper wire,  Siemens  Bentex, L/T, Schneider,  Wanding  Materials and all kinds of industrial electric parts.]]></description>
	<dc:creator>superadmin</dc:creator>
	<pubDate>Fri, 20 Dec 2019 06:16:03 +0100</pubDate>
	<guid>https://pudirectory.com/electronics/2736-new-mahaveer-electricals</guid>
</item>
<item>
	<title>Food Station</title>
	<link>https://pudirectory.com/restaurants/2704-food-station</link>
	<description><![CDATA["we deliver food at your desired place any time, anywhere also easier than ever". Save time Save money.

"Food station" is an online food delivery company in Biratnagar, with the aim of delivering any food o your choice at your desired place as quick as possible with the development o technology and emerging growth of online services.

Established to serving and delivering  the best food  in Biratnagar. ]]></description>
	<dc:creator>prakash</dc:creator>
	<pubDate>Mon, 16 Dec 2019 08:20:21 +0100</pubDate>
	<guid>https://pudirectory.com/restaurants/2704-food-station</guid>
</item>
<item>
	<title>KinderPillar</title>
	<link>https://pudirectory.com/education/montessori/2444-kinderpillar</link>
	<description><![CDATA[<img align="right" src="https://pudirectory.com/media/com_mtree/images/listings/s/623.jpg" alt="KinderPillar" />Kinder Pillar Ivy league is the first  American-Format preschool in Itahari. We provide world class ambiance with modern facilities.
Safe and secure environment with CCTV camera in each classrooms with hygienic fooding facility ,Attractive play areas with the teacher child ratio 1:10, kinder smart class, Splash pool, Toy library, Karate classes, French language classes, Own school bus, Day care Facility.
]]></description>
	<dc:creator>jeena</dc:creator>
	<pubDate>Mon, 16 Dec 2019 05:52:11 +0100</pubDate>
	<guid>https://pudirectory.com/education/montessori/2444-kinderpillar</guid>
</item>
<item>
	<title>RONGO'S MOMO HUT</title>
	<link>https://pudirectory.com/restaurants/906-rongo-s-momo-hut</link>
	<description><![CDATA[fast food restaurant ]]></description>
	<dc:creator>superadmin</dc:creator>
	<pubDate>Sun, 08 Dec 2019 08:44:49 +0100</pubDate>
	<guid>https://pudirectory.com/restaurants/906-rongo-s-momo-hut</guid>
</item>
<item>
	<title>MULTY PLY</title>
	<link>https://pudirectory.com/furniture/2647-multy-ply</link>
	<description><![CDATA[<img align="right" src="https://pudirectory.com/media/com_mtree/images/listings/s/644.jpg" alt="MULTY PLY" />We are manufacturer of all kinds of furniture if u r planing to make furniture's then remember us . We are here for:-
Ne-Ply (Nepal most trusted plywood)
Doors and windows fitting
And all kind of furniture...]]></description>
	<dc:creator>prakash</dc:creator>
	<pubDate>Fri, 06 Dec 2019 08:05:31 +0100</pubDate>
	<guid>https://pudirectory.com/furniture/2647-multy-ply</guid>
</item>
<item>
	<title>Nazarian Law Firm</title>
	<link>https://pudirectory.com/legal-forms/973-nazarian-law-firm</link>
	<description><![CDATA[The Nazarian Law Firm handles all forms of litigation and transactions. We define our work on the important principle that we care for every client and their legal needs. Serving in Orange County, Los Angeles and San Diego Counties, we pride ourselves on being able to intelligently and passionatley represent anyone.]]></description>
	<dc:creator>superadmin</dc:creator>
	<pubDate>Sun, 01 Dec 2019 08:35:55 +0100</pubDate>
	<guid>https://pudirectory.com/legal-forms/973-nazarian-law-firm</guid>
</item>
<item>
	<title>Exciting Nepal Treks and Expedition P.Ltd.</title>
	<link>https://pudirectory.com/travel-agencies/968-exciting-nepal-treks-and-expedition-p-ltd</link>
	<description><![CDATA[Exciting Nepal Treks & Expedition Pvt. Ltd. is located in Kathmandu. Exciting Nepal Treks & Expedition Pvt. Ltd. is working in Travel agencies activities. You can contact the company at 01-4701298. You can find more information about Exciting Nepal Treks & Expedition Pvt. Ltd. at www.excitingnepal.com. You can contact the company by email at info@excitingnepal.com.]]></description>
	<dc:creator>superadmin</dc:creator>
	<pubDate>Sun, 01 Dec 2019 08:32:55 +0100</pubDate>
	<guid>https://pudirectory.com/travel-agencies/968-exciting-nepal-treks-and-expedition-p-ltd</guid>
</item>
<item>
	<title>The Hygiene Cafe</title>
	<link>https://pudirectory.com/restaurants/2604-the-hygiene-cafe</link>
	<description><![CDATA[<img align="right" src="https://pudirectory.com/media/com_mtree/images/listings/s/642.jpg" alt="The Hygiene Cafe" />The Hygiene Cafe  Specialty  for  Best Biryani & Thakali  food  and  continental. 
]]></description>
	<dc:creator>prakash</dc:creator>
	<pubDate>Sun, 01 Dec 2019 06:55:29 +0100</pubDate>
	<guid>https://pudirectory.com/restaurants/2604-the-hygiene-cafe</guid>
</item>
<item>
	<title>JAYA GANGA TOURS &amp; TRAVEL(PVT.LTD)</title>
	<link>https://pudirectory.com/travel-agencies/2568-jaya-ganga-tours-travel-pvt-ltd</link>
	<description><![CDATA[<img align="right" src="https://pudirectory.com/media/com_mtree/images/listings/s/641.jpeg" alt="JAYA GANGA TOURS & TRAVEL(PVT.LTD)" />Jaya Ganga tours & travels: - looking for business travels packages. Let us help you find great results! Your travels experience is our priority.
We are here for:
 Train tickets, Domestic & International Flights, Visa process and Tour packages. 
]]></description>
	<dc:creator>prakash</dc:creator>
	<pubDate>Tue, 26 Nov 2019 14:43:01 +0100</pubDate>
	<guid>https://pudirectory.com/travel-agencies/2568-jaya-ganga-tours-travel-pvt-ltd</guid>
</item>
<item>
	<title>Hamro Boutique</title>
	<link>https://pudirectory.com/clothing/2567-hamro-boutique</link>
	<description><![CDATA[<img align="right" src="https://pudirectory.com/media/com_mtree/images/listings/s/640.jpg" alt="Hamro Boutique" />Hamro boutique: - Clothes that is versatile enough for a day with girls, women , all women wear. Ultimate destination for Ethnic wear, best known for Bridal wear.  ]]></description>
	<dc:creator>prakash</dc:creator>
	<pubDate>Tue, 26 Nov 2019 14:16:28 +0100</pubDate>
	<guid>https://pudirectory.com/clothing/2567-hamro-boutique</guid>
</item>
<item>
	<title>Hotel Namaskar</title>
	<link>https://pudirectory.com/hotels/138-hotel-namaskar</link>
	<description><![CDATA[<img align="right" src="https://pudirectory.com/media/com_mtree/images/listings/s/107.jpg" alt="Hotel Namaskar" />Hotel Namaskar is located at the heart of Biratnagar Traffic Chowk. We overlook Biratnagar market and offer stunning views from our rooms. The hotel is close to Biratnagar’s attractions, such as cinema hall and historical palace of King Askoka to vibrant shopping malls of Traffic Chowk Street and  Main Road area.
 
Hotel Namaskar on Traffic Chowk is famed for its service and prestigious Market location. Boasting a range of famous Biratnagar restaurants and bars, our hotel offers a culinary journey starting with breakfast at Hotel Namaskar itself. Sample our Confessions of a delicious afternoon tea, followed by drinks in our designer Bar.
 
Hotel Namaskar offers a wide range of meetings and event space for any occasion, from small business meetings to glamorous award dinners and stylish weddings.
The rooms here are cozy and all rooms have AC ( air condition) to deal with the humid weather conditions where temperature rises to an extent of 41 degrees centigrade. Every room consists of attached bathrooms and television with cable connection. Going with the trend we also provide free Wi-Fi in the hotel premises to help you updated with what's going on in the cyber world.]]></description>
	<dc:creator>superadmin</dc:creator>
	<pubDate>Thu, 21 Nov 2019 06:19:21 +0100</pubDate>
	<guid>https://pudirectory.com/hotels/138-hotel-namaskar</guid>
</item>
<item>
	<title>K media</title>
	<link>https://pudirectory.com/advertising-agencies/2439-k-media</link>
	<description><![CDATA[<img align="right" src="https://pudirectory.com/media/com_mtree/images/listings/s/622.jpg" alt="K media" />K media is an Advertising company which works for the creative video, advertisement, Conceptual video Advertisement, Magazine in Biratnagar.
]]></description>
	<dc:creator>jeena</dc:creator>
	<pubDate>Wed, 06 Nov 2019 10:20:50 +0100</pubDate>
	<guid>https://pudirectory.com/advertising-agencies/2439-k-media</guid>
</item>
<item>
	<title>Oldpinch Online Shopping</title>
	<link>https://pudirectory.com/shopping/949-oldpinch-online-shopping</link>
	<description><![CDATA[<img align="right" src="https://pudirectory.com/media/com_mtree/images/listings/s/458.jpg" alt="Oldpinch Online Shopping" />eCommerce website https://www.oldpinch.com which sells various electronic products and cosmetic products at very reasonable price.Free home delivery inside Kathmandu and delivery all over Nepal. Quality products at very best prices. Easy Return policies and own ware house.]]></description>
	<dc:creator>superadmin</dc:creator>
	<pubDate>Fri, 14 Jun 2019 08:38:18 +0100</pubDate>
	<guid>https://pudirectory.com/shopping/949-oldpinch-online-shopping</guid>
</item>
<item>
	<title>Global Holidays Adventure</title>
	<link>https://pudirectory.com/travel-agencies/948-global-holidays-adventure</link>
	<description><![CDATA[<img align="right" src="https://pudirectory.com/media/com_mtree/images/listings/s/457.jpg" alt="Global Holidays Adventure" />Global Holidays Adventure Pvt. Ltd is a government registered trekking company adminstered by the highly qualified, motivated and result-oriented professional trekking and tour leaders of Nepal to promote adventure tourism within Nepal, Tibet and Bhutan.]]></description>
	<dc:creator>superadmin</dc:creator>
	<pubDate>Fri, 14 Jun 2019 08:37:56 +0100</pubDate>
	<guid>https://pudirectory.com/travel-agencies/948-global-holidays-adventure</guid>
</item>
<item>
	<title>Licenders - Long Island</title>
	<link>https://pudirectory.com/beauty-spa/958-licenders-long-island</link>
	<description><![CDATA[Licenders takes care of head lice removal with 100% all natural products and professional safe free screenings in fiive convenient Tri-State area locations. We provide kid friendly salons with fully credentialed lice clinicians who have kids too! We provide lice treatment and removal products used by our clinicians in the Licenders Store to make home treatment even easier.]]></description>
	<dc:creator>superadmin</dc:creator>
	<pubDate>Mon, 20 May 2019 08:38:17 +0100</pubDate>
	<guid>https://pudirectory.com/beauty-spa/958-licenders-long-island</guid>
</item>
<item>
	<title>United Shipping &amp; Forwarding Service P. Ltd</title>
	<link>https://pudirectory.com/transportation/950-united-shipping-forwarding-service-p-ltd</link>
	<description><![CDATA[ leading Freight Forwarding and Logistics Company ]]></description>
	<dc:creator>superadmin</dc:creator>
	<pubDate>Mon, 20 May 2019 08:35:14 +0100</pubDate>
	<guid>https://pudirectory.com/transportation/950-united-shipping-forwarding-service-p-ltd</guid>
</item>
<item>
	<title>Global Holidays Adventure</title>
	<link>https://pudirectory.com/travel-agencies/947-global-holidays-adventure</link>
	<description><![CDATA[<img align="right" src="https://pudirectory.com/media/com_mtree/images/listings/s/456.jpg" alt="Global Holidays Adventure" />Global Holidays Adventure Pvt. Ltd is a government registered trekking company adminstered by the highly qualified, motivated and result-oriented professional trekking and tour leaders of Nepal to promote adventure tourism within Nepal, Tibet and Bhutan.]]></description>
	<dc:creator>superadmin</dc:creator>
	<pubDate>Mon, 20 May 2019 08:29:07 +0100</pubDate>
	<guid>https://pudirectory.com/travel-agencies/947-global-holidays-adventure</guid>
</item>
<item>
	<title>Delta Tech Nepal</title>
	<link>https://pudirectory.com/computers/1127-delta-tech-nepal</link>
	<description><![CDATA[Delta Tech is a Nepal based web and mobile apps development company, and is led by professionals that have come back to Nepal from various destinations after building expertise in the field of IT. Every website and mobile app that we create is designed and built in-house by our team of experienced designers and developers. Our main areas of expertise include designing corporate websites, providing e-commerce solutions, developing web and mobile applications. Having done numerous work in the above areas, we focus on delivering high quality IT services to our clients.]]></description>
	<dc:creator>superadmin</dc:creator>
	<pubDate>Thu, 11 Apr 2019 13:03:30 +0100</pubDate>
	<guid>https://pudirectory.com/computers/1127-delta-tech-nepal</guid>
</item>
<item>
	<title>Central Mall</title>
	<link>https://pudirectory.com/shopping/1400-central-mall</link>
	<description><![CDATA[<img align="right" src="https://pudirectory.com/media/com_mtree/images/listings/s/538.jpg" alt="Central Mall" />In order to bring back the Glory of the City, 3 prominent business houses, Debenara Group, Vishal group, and Hi-Life group joined hands to develop an International Standard Mall and Multiplex at the Heart of the Biratnagar City, and named it Central Mall, Central Multiplex. Central Mall is designed as the retail redefinition of Biratnagar, an International Standard of shopping & entertainment destination with a built up area of 1 Lakh 34 thousand square feet.

 

Central Mall is the first premium retail & entertainment destination mall in Biratnagar. It has been designed to complement the changing perspectives and lifestyles of modern-day Biratnagar with state-of-the-art building systems and a superior design balancing the contemporary architecture. It stands as a symbol of positive growth and it is a Multi-utility commercial complex comprising a wide range of luxury Brand Outlets, Department Store, Food Court, Entertainment Zones, 2-Screen Multiplex and Sky lounge & Bar – all come together in the upmarket Main road -7 to offer the epitome of Hospitality not just in Birat but in the state no.1.Central Mall has earned the Destination of being the City's only organized Fashion Destination.
]]></description>
	<dc:creator>superadmin</dc:creator>
	<pubDate>Mon, 08 Apr 2019 13:53:48 +0100</pubDate>
	<guid>https://pudirectory.com/shopping/1400-central-mall</guid>
</item>
<item>
	<title>Central Multiplex</title>
	<link>https://pudirectory.com/movies/1305-central-multiplex</link>
	<description><![CDATA[<img align="right" src="https://pudirectory.com/media/com_mtree/images/listings/s/533.jpg" alt="Central Multiplex" />With the launch of Central Multiplex,
we have added a new name to the list of movie destinations in Biratnagar.
This multiplex is the first standard multiplex from Central Multiplex.


    Central Multiplex Pvt. Ltd.
    Main Road, Biratnagar -7, Nepal
    info@centralmultiplex.com.np
    021-534008, 021-534009
]]></description>
	<dc:creator>superadmin</dc:creator>
	<pubDate>Mon, 08 Apr 2019 13:42:31 +0100</pubDate>
	<guid>https://pudirectory.com/movies/1305-central-multiplex</guid>
</item>
<item>
	<title>The Mother Baby Center</title>
	<link>https://pudirectory.com/ngo-ingo/943-the-mother-baby-center</link>
	<description><![CDATA[We welcome you, your family, and your baby to our Coon Rapids location at Mercy Hospital with Children’s Minnesota. At The Mother Baby Center, pregnancy, childbirth and neonatal experts provide a unique, personalized experience and top-notch care throughout your childbirth journey. Our birth center is a comfortable and inviting place designed with you in mind, so you can welcome your little one into the world knowing that you and baby have the best care.
Whether you’re a first-time mom or an experienced one, The Mother Baby Center at Mercy in Coon Rapids wants to help create the birthing experience you envision. We promise to listen to your concerns and needs, and do the very best we can to exceed your expectations. We offer labor and delivery care for routine and high-risk pregnancies; home health services, integrative services, newborn care, and pain management services with non-medicinal options. For families whose babies need higher levels of care, we offer neonatal intensive care provided by pediatric experts from Children’s Minnesota.]]></description>
	<dc:creator>superadmin</dc:creator>
	<pubDate>Wed, 27 Mar 2019 08:19:31 +0100</pubDate>
	<guid>https://pudirectory.com/ngo-ingo/943-the-mother-baby-center</guid>
</item>
<item>
	<title>Care Builders at Home Minnesota</title>
	<link>https://pudirectory.com/hotels/942-carebuilders-at-home-minnesota</link>
	<description><![CDATA[CareBuilders at Home Minneapolis, Minnesota is your partner for efficient, home care assistance in Minnesota. We provide a full range of services that help make life easier for you and your loved ones.]]></description>
	<dc:creator>superadmin</dc:creator>
	<pubDate>Wed, 27 Mar 2019 08:18:50 +0100</pubDate>
	<guid>https://pudirectory.com/hotels/942-carebuilders-at-home-minnesota</guid>
</item>
<item>
	<title>Care Builders at Home Plano Frisco</title>
	<link>https://pudirectory.com/medical-shops/941-carebuilders-at-home-plano-frisco</link>
	<description><![CDATA[Carebuilders at Home Plano-Frisco locally owned franchise that provides home care solutions to our seniors and the community. Whether for long or short term help, making your home care experience a positive one is our highest priority.
]]></description>
	<dc:creator>superadmin</dc:creator>
	<pubDate>Wed, 27 Mar 2019 08:17:11 +0100</pubDate>
	<guid>https://pudirectory.com/medical-shops/941-carebuilders-at-home-plano-frisco</guid>
</item>
</channel>
</rss>
