<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/" xmlns:mtree="http://www.mosets.com/tree/rss/">
<channel>
<title>Purbanchal Directory - Recently Added Listings - Airlines</title>
<description></description>
<link>https://pudirectory.com/</link>
<lastBuildDate>Sat, 25 Apr 2020 12:40:38 +0100</lastBuildDate>
<generator>FeedCreator 1.7.3</generator>
<item>
	<title>Yeti Airlines</title>
	<link>https://pudirectory.com/airlines/14-yeti-airlines</link>
	<description><![CDATA[Biratnagar, a sub-metropolitan and Nepal’s second largest city is located in Koshi Zone on the southern Terai belt of Nepal, near the south-eastern border with India.

One can get here from Kathmandu by road and air. Biratnagar Airport is the regional hub for vital air services serving the remote Eastern Hills, and there are regular flights to Kathmandu.

The Koshi Tappu Wildlife Reserve (90-minute drive) is a bird-watching spot. The Koshi Barrage on the Koshi River (two-hour drive) is an impressive sight. Biratnagar is the hub of air routes in eastern Nepal.

Biratnagar
Sales Office: 021 - 536612 / 536613
Airport: 021 - 460769
Fax: 021 - 440024]]></description>
	<dc:creator>superadmin</dc:creator>
	<pubDate>Sat, 10 Dec 2016 06:31:59 +0100</pubDate>
	<guid>https://pudirectory.com/airlines/14-yeti-airlines</guid>
</item>
<item>
	<title>Nepal Airlines</title>
	<link>https://pudirectory.com/airlines/13-nepal-airlines</link>
	<description><![CDATA[Nepal Airlines
Nepal Airlines Corporation (NAC) was incorporated on 1 July 1958 through enactment of Nepal Airlines Corporation Act. 2019 with the following main objective:

to provide air transport service to any person, agency or organization who need such service for transportation of men or materials from one airport to another either within or outside the country.

Profile of Aircrafts used in NAC services.

-----------------------------------------------
Eastern Regional Centre :

Biratnagar
Mr. Bil Bahadur Shrestha
Ph. No. 021 470661, 021 470336

Bhojpur
Mr. Laxman Raj Sitaula
Ph No. 029 420167
Mob: 9841595069

Phaplu
Mr. Dilip Raj Sharma
Ph No. 038 520167
Mob: 9743022167

Rumjatar
Mr. Bandhu Raj Neupane
Ph No. 037 540114
Mob: 9741061703

Taplejung
Mr Hemant K. Upreti
Ph No. 024 460167
Mob: 9741163938

Lamidanda
Mr Ramesh Shrestha
Ph No. 036 690205,
Mob: 9741046299

Tumlingtar
Ph No. 029 569167, 0129 575167
Mob: 9742040481

Kangeldanda
Mob: 9741068402

Thamkharka
Mr. Man Singh Bohara
Ph No. 033 620985
Mob: 9741823587

Khanidanda
Mr Yadav Sen Rai
Mob: 9743001494
------------------------------------]]></description>
	<dc:creator>superadmin</dc:creator>
	<pubDate>Sat, 10 Dec 2016 06:29:18 +0100</pubDate>
	<guid>https://pudirectory.com/airlines/13-nepal-airlines</guid>
</item>
<item>
	<title>Buddha Air</title>
	<link>https://pudirectory.com/airlines/12-buddha-air</link>
	<description><![CDATA[Buddha Air
Buddha Air operates in only fully navigational aid equipped asphalt airports with more than 3700 feet runway length.

servicesBuddha Air has prided itself in maintaining safety as the highest priority. Pilots and engineers are sent on regular training programs directly to the manufacturing companies for the ATR and Beech craft training. Buddha Air makes no monetary compromise on the aircraft’s maintenance and each aircraft is thoroughly checked before every take off and after every landing.

The Beech craft 1900D, ATR 42-320 and ATR 72-500 have their own unique inspection procedure. Qualified and certified aircraft maintenance engineers with many years of experience from the company’s Engineering Department carry out a detailed daily safety inspection check that follows the following standard procedure as mentioned in the current Nepalese Civil Airworthiness Requirement and the aircraft’s maintenance manual given by the manufacturer. After each check has been done as per the requirement, the technician gets the form signed by the head of the Department. If there is even the slightest technical fault the flight is halted and passengers are flown in another aircraft that has passed the daily inspection routine. Besides the daily inspection routine the aircrafts are also checked during every transit of the operation. For the assurance of our clients we have listed the details of the procedure below.

Biratnagar
Tel: 021-526901, 021-530866
Fax: 021-530866
Email: biratnagar@buddhaair.com
Airport: 021-460478]]></description>
	<dc:creator>superadmin</dc:creator>
	<pubDate>Sat, 10 Dec 2016 06:27:16 +0100</pubDate>
	<guid>https://pudirectory.com/airlines/12-buddha-air</guid>
</item>
</channel>
</rss>
